[
    {
        "question": "Which city has the most clubs competing in its country's top Division?",
        " first_option": "Liverpool",
        " second_option": "London",
        " third_option": "Manchester",
        " answer": "London",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  How many of the 20 clubs in MLS, are based in Canada? ",
        " first_option": "Five",
        " second_option": "Three",
        " third_option": "Seven",
        " answer": "Three",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  In which country would you find the World's largest football stadium (by capacity)?",
        " first_option": "China",
        " second_option": "North Korea",
        " third_option": "Spain",
        " answer": "North Korea",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which club has been Croatian league champions for the last 10 years?",
        " first_option": "Slaven Belupo",
        " second_option": "Dinamo Zagreb",
        " third_option": "HNK Rijeka",
        " answer": "Dinamo Zagreb",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Who finished the 2014/15 Ligue 1 season as a top scorer?",
        " first_option": "Zlatan Ibrahimovic",
        " second_option": "Alexandre Lacazette",
        " third_option": "Edinson Cavani",
        " answer": "Alexandre Lacazette",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which club has won the most Serie A titles?",
        " first_option": "Inter ",
        " second_option": "Juventus",
        " third_option": "Milan",
        " answer": "Juventus",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which of the following English Players has played for Lazio?",
        " first_option": "Paul Ince",
        " second_option": "Paul Gasciogne",
        " third_option": "Micah Richards",
        " answer": "Paul Gasciogne",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which UK-player captained Iceland during their first European championship Qualifier?",
        " first_option": "Glyfi Sigurdsson",
        " second_option": "Aron Gunnarson",
        " third_option": "Eidur Gudjohnsen",
        " answer": "Aron Gunnarson",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which country won the 2015 Africa Cup of Nations?",
        " first_option": "Ghana",
        " second_option": "Ivory Coast",
        " third_option": "Egypt",
        " answer": "Ivory Coast",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  The African Champions league was won by TP Mazembe in 2015. Which country are they from?",
        " first_option": "Kenya ",
        " second_option": "DRC",
        " third_option": "South Africa",
        " answer": "DRC",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Who was the last French club to play in a champions league final?",
        " first_option": "Paris Saint-Germain",
        " second_option": "AS Monaco",
        " third_option": "Marseille",
        " answer": "AS Monaco",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Diego Forlan signed for which Japanese club in 2014?",
        " first_option": "FC tokyo",
        " second_option": "Cerezo Osaka",
        " third_option": "Jubilo Iwata",
        " answer": "Cerezo Osaka",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  In what country would you find the home of FC Santa Claus?",
        " first_option": "Sweden ",
        " second_option": "Finland ",
        " third_option": "Norway",
        " answer": "Finland ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Milan legend George Weah represented which African Nation?",
        " first_option": "Sierra Leone",
        " second_option": "Liberia",
        " third_option": "Ghana",
        " answer": "Liberia",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  In what year did a Dutch Club last win a European club competition?",
        " first_option": "1997",
        " second_option": "2002",
        " third_option": "1978",
        " answer": "2002",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which Dutch team was the last to win a European club competition?",
        " first_option": "Ajax",
        " second_option": "Feyenoord",
        " third_option": "Twente",
        " answer": "Feyenoord",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which club won the MLS Cup in 2015? ",
        " first_option": "LA Galaxy",
        " second_option": "Portland Timbers",
        " third_option": "Colorado Rapids",
        " answer": "Portland Timbers",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which Argentinian team has won the most Copa Libertadores ?",
        " first_option": "River Plate ",
        " second_option": "Boca Juniors",
        " third_option": "Santos",
        " answer": "Boca Juniors",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Riyad Mahrez was signed to Leicester city from which club?",
        " first_option": "Sporting Lisbon",
        " second_option": "Le Havre",
        " third_option": "Marseille",
        " answer": "Le Havre",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Who are the only International team to have retained the European championship?",
        " first_option": "Holland",
        " second_option": "Spain ",
        " third_option": "Germany",
        " answer": "Spain ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Massimiliano Vieri, brother of Christian Vieri, represented which international Team?",
        " first_option": "Italy",
        " second_option": "Australia",
        " third_option": "France",
        " answer": "Australia",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Who won the German Cup in the 2015 season?",
        " first_option": "Borussia Dortmund",
        " second_option": "VfL Wolfsburg",
        " third_option": "Bayern Munich",
        " answer": "VfL Wolfsburg",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which of these players was born in England?",
        " first_option": "Raheem Sterling ",
        " second_option": "Vinnie Jones",
        " third_option": "Owen Hargreaves",
        " answer": "Vinnie Jones",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which of these South American countries has never qualified for a World cup?",
        " first_option": "Bolivia ",
        " second_option": "Venezuela",
        " third_option": "Ecuador",
        " answer": "Venezuela",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  In the 2010 World cup, who were the only side to be knocked out of the group stage unbeaten?",
        " first_option": "North Korea",
        " second_option": "New Zealand",
        " third_option": "Italy",
        " answer": "New Zealand",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Who is the only goalkeeper to have won the Ballon d'Or?",
        " first_option": "Peter Shilton",
        " second_option": "Lev Yashin",
        " third_option": "Iker Casillas",
        " answer": "Lev Yashin",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which English player has scored the most goals in a single MLS season?",
        " first_option": "Jermaine Defoe",
        " second_option": "David Beckham",
        " third_option": "Bradley Wright Phillips",
        " answer": "David Beckham",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  In which Brazilian city is the club Vasco de Gama based?",
        " first_option": "Porto Alegre",
        " second_option": "Rio de Janeiro",
        " third_option": "Sao Paolo",
        " answer": "Rio de Janeiro",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Petr Cech started his career with which Czech club?",
        " first_option": "Slavia Prague",
        " second_option": "Viktoria Plzen",
        " third_option": "Sparta Prague",
        " answer": "Viktoria Plzen",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which Caribbean Island was the first to qualify for a World cup?",
        " first_option": "Cuba ",
        " second_option": "Haiti ",
        " third_option": "Jamaica",
        " answer": "Haiti ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which country Third in the World cup in 2014?",
        " first_option": "Argentina",
        " second_option": "Holland ",
        " third_option": "Brazil",
        " answer": "Holland ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Gary Neville started his first managerial job at which Spanish club? ",
        " first_option": "Granada",
        " second_option": "Real Sociedad",
        " third_option": "Valencia",
        " answer": "Valencia",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which Greek club has reached a European Cup final?",
        " first_option": "PAOK FC",
        " second_option": "Olympiakos",
        " third_option": "Panathinaikos",
        " answer": "Panathinaikos",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which was the last English club to win the Europa League?",
        " first_option": "Manchester United",
        " second_option": "Liverpool",
        " third_option": "Chelsea",
        " answer": "Chelsea",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Lionel Messi was born in which city?",
        " first_option": "Barcelona",
        " second_option": "Beunos Aires",
        " third_option": "Rosario",
        " answer": "Rosario",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Chile won the Copa America in 2015. How many times have they won the tournament?",
        " first_option": "Three Times",
        " second_option": "One Time ",
        " third_option": "Two times ",
        " answer": "Two times ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which country won the Asian Cup of Nations for the first time in 2017?",
        " first_option": "Saudi Arabia",
        " second_option": "Iran",
        " third_option": "Iraq",
        " answer": "Iraq",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which country was top of FIFA's World rankings at the start of 2016?",
        " first_option": "Blegium",
        " second_option": "Germany",
        " third_option": "Argentina",
        " answer": "Argentina",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Claudio Ranieri coached which of these countries?",
        " first_option": "Romania",
        " second_option": "Faroe Islands",
        " third_option": "Greece",
        " answer": "Greece",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which city is home to three La Liga Clubs?",
        " first_option": "Seville",
        " second_option": "Barcelona ",
        " third_option": "Madrid",
        " answer": "Madrid",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Name the largest country in terms of population, who have never played in a World Cup?",
        " first_option": "Bangladesh",
        " second_option": "Indonesia",
        " third_option": "India",
        " answer": "India",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Former Ballon d'Or winner Andriy Shevchenko is from which nation?",
        " first_option": "Belarus ",
        " second_option": "Russia ",
        " third_option": "Ukraine",
        " answer": "Ukraine",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which of the following countries is yet to produce a Ballon d'Or winner?",
        " first_option": "Denmark ",
        " second_option": "Bulgaria ",
        " third_option": "Sweden",
        " answer": "Sweden",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which of these players is England's Top Goalscorer?",
        " first_option": "Harry Kane",
        " second_option": "Gary Lineker",
        " third_option": "Wayne Rooney",
        " answer": "Wayne Rooney",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  The 2022 World Cup will be held in which country?",
        " first_option": "U.A.E",
        " second_option": "Saudi Arabia",
        " third_option": "Qatar",
        " answer": "Qatar",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Which of these teams has hosted the FIFA World Cup without previously competing in it?",
        " first_option": "Switzerland",
        " second_option": "South Africa",
        " third_option": "Uruguay",
        " answer": "Uruguay",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Who was the first non-European to win the Ballon d'Or?",
        " first_option": "Maradonna",
        " second_option": "Pele",
        " third_option": "George Weah",
        " answer": "George Weah",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Who won the 1998 FIFA World Cup?",
        " first_option": "Italy ",
        " second_option": "Germany",
        " third_option": "France",
        " answer": "France",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Who won the 2014/15 English Premier League Title?",
        " first_option": "Manchester United",
        " second_option": "Manchester City",
        " third_option": "Chelsea",
        " answer": "Chelsea",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "  Who won the 2015 Women's FIFA World Cup? ",
        " first_option": "Germany",
        " second_option": "Canada",
        " third_option": "USA",
        " answer": "USA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the European Championship's all-time top scorer ?",
        " first_option": "Thierry Henry",
        " second_option": "Marco Van Basten ",
        " third_option": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        " answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the New Den?",
        " first_option": "Bournemouth",
        " second_option": "West Ham",
        " third_option": "Millwall",
        " answer": "Millwall",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the tottenham hotspur stadium?",
        " first_option": "West Ham",
        " second_option": "Chelsea",
        " third_option": "Tottenham Hotspur ",
        " answer": "Tottenham Hotspur ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Stamford Bridge?",
        " first_option": "Millwall",
        " second_option": "West Ham",
        " third_option": "Chelsea",
        " answer": "Chelsea",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who played their home UEFA games at the Luzhniki Stadium till 2013?",
        " first_option": "Redstar Belgrade",
        " second_option": "Zenith st. Petersburg",
        " third_option": "CSKA Moscow",
        " answer": "CSKA Moscow",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Stade Louis II?",
        " first_option": "Caen",
        " second_option": "Le Havre",
        " third_option": "AS Monaco",
        " answer": "AS Monaco",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Friends Arena?",
        " first_option": "Feyenoord",
        " second_option": "Benfica",
        " third_option": "Allsvenskan AIK club",
        " answer": "Allsvenskan AIK club",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Estadio da Luz?",
        " first_option": "Valencia",
        " second_option": "Malaga",
        " third_option": "Benfica",
        " answer": "Benfica",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Stadion Feijenoord?",
        " first_option": "Allsvenskan AIK club",
        " second_option": "Arsenal",
        " third_option": "Feyenoord",
        " answer": "Feyenoord",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the  London Stadium?",
        " first_option": "Tottenham Hotspur",
        " second_option": "Chelsea",
        " third_option": "West Ham United",
        " answer": "West Ham United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Parken?",
        " first_option": "Benefica",
        " second_option": "Feyenoord",
        " third_option": "FC Copenhagen",
        " answer": "FC Copenhagen",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the St. James Park?",
        " first_option": "Millwall",
        " second_option": "West Ham",
        " third_option": "Newcastle",
        " answer": "Newcastle",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Groupama Stadium?",
        " first_option": "LA Galaxy",
        " second_option": "Ajax",
        " third_option": "Lyon",
        " answer": "Lyon",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Sukru Saracoglu?",
        " first_option": "ALlsvenskan AIK club",
        " second_option": "Feyenoord",
        " third_option": "Fenerbahce",
        " answer": "Fenerbahce",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Goodison Park?",
        " first_option": "Millwall",
        " second_option": "Liverpool",
        " third_option": "Everton",
        " answer": "Everton",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Olympiastadion?",
        " first_option": "Zenith st. Petersburg",
        " second_option": "RZ Liepzig",
        " third_option": "Hertha Berlin",
        " answer": "Hertha Berlin",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Veltins-Arena?",
        " first_option": "Allsvenskan AIK club",
        " second_option": "Feyenoord",
        " third_option": "Schalke",
        " answer": "Schalke",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Celtic Park?",
        " first_option": "Rangers",
        " second_option": "Motherwell",
        " third_option": "Celtic",
        " answer": "Celtic",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Allianz Stadium?",
        " first_option": "Roma",
        " second_option": "Lazio",
        " third_option": "Juventus",
        " answer": "Juventus",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Principality Stadium?",
        " first_option": "Lithuania",
        " second_option": "England",
        " third_option": "Wales",
        " answer": "Wales",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Allianz Arena?",
        " first_option": "Schalke",
        " second_option": "LA Galaxy",
        " third_option": "Bayern Munich",
        " answer": "Bayern Munich",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Mestalla?",
        " first_option": "Sevilla",
        " second_option": "Malaga",
        " third_option": "Valencia",
        " answer": "Valencia",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the San Siro?",
        " first_option": "Roma",
        " second_option": "Lazio",
        " third_option": "AC milan",
        " answer": "AC milan",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Signal Iduna Park?",
        " first_option": "RZ Liepzig",
        " second_option": "HNK Rijeka",
        " third_option": "Borrusia Dortmund",
        " answer": "Borrusia Dortmund",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the Le Parc des Princes?",
        " first_option": "Ajax",
        " second_option": "Lyon",
        " third_option": "Paris Saint-Germain",
        " answer": "Paris Saint-Germain",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who plays home games at the M.K.O Abiola National Stadium?",
        " first_option": "Benin",
        " second_option": "Togo",
        " third_option": "Nigeria",
        " answer": "Nigeria",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What color are Wales' international home shirts?\t  ",
        " first_option": "White",
        " second_option": "Black ",
        " third_option": "Red",
        " answer": "Red",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In which year did Arsene Wenger join Arsenal as manager?",
        " first_option": "1998",
        " second_option": "1994",
        " third_option": "1996",
        " answer": "1996",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the \"PLAYER OF THE SEASON\", for the 2014/2015 English premier league season ?",
        " first_option": "Luis Suarez",
        " second_option": "Frank Lampard",
        " third_option": "Eden Hazard",
        " answer": "Eden Hazard",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "At which club were Niall Quinn & Kevin Philips strikers?",
        " first_option": "Everton",
        " second_option": "Arsenal",
        " third_option": "Sunderland",
        " answer": "Sunderland",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which was the first English club to install an artificial pitch?",
        " first_option": "Arsenal ",
        " second_option": "Chelsea",
        " third_option": "QPR",
        " answer": "QPR",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city has a team of the same name as a United team?\n",
        " first_option": "Leceister",
        " second_option": "York",
        " third_option": "Dundee",
        " answer": "Dundee",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hernan Crespo joined Chelsea in 2003 from which club?",
        " first_option": "Napoli",
        " second_option": "AC Milan",
        " third_option": "Inter Milan",
        " answer": "Inter Milan",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many consecutive goals did Jamie Vardy scored in the 2015/2016 season, setting up a new Premier League record?\n",
        " first_option": "9",
        " second_option": "14",
        " third_option": "11",
        " answer": "11",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who scored England's goal against Brazil in the 2002 World Cup?",
        " first_option": "John Barnes",
        " second_option": "David Beckham",
        " third_option": "Micheal Owen",
        " answer": "Micheal Owen",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who managed Liverpool to the 1986 FA Cup and League double?",
        " first_option": "Jurgen Klopp",
        " second_option": "Bob Paisley",
        " third_option": "Kenny Dalgish",
        " answer": "Kenny Dalgish",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was Chelsea manager when they won 2013 Europa League?",
        " first_option": "Robert Di Matteo",
        " second_option": "Jose Mourinho",
        " third_option": "Rafa Benitez",
        " answer": "Rafa Benitez",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Where did Man Utd finish in the 2017/18 season?",
        " first_option": "10th",
        " second_option": "6th",
        " third_option": "2nd",
        " answer": "2nd",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these clubs has Zlatan Ibrahimovic NOT played for?",
        " first_option": "Juventus",
        " second_option": "Ajax",
        " third_option": "Bayern Munich",
        " answer": "Bayern Munich",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was Leicester City's captain when they won the 2015/16 premier league?",
        " first_option": "Kasper Schmeichel",
        " second_option": "Jamie Vardy",
        " third_option": "Wes Morgan ",
        " answer": "Wes Morgan ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Andy Carroll left Newcastle for which club in January 2011?",
        " first_option": "Newcastle",
        " second_option": "West Ham",
        " third_option": "Liverpool",
        " answer": "Liverpool",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Carlos Tevez played for which 3 premier league clubs?",
        " first_option": "Aston Villa, Tottenham, Man. United",
        " second_option": "Newcastle, Man. City, Man.United",
        " third_option": "West Ham, Man. City, Man. United",
        " answer": "West Ham, Man. City, Man. United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jurgen Klopps first win as manager of Liverpool came against which club?",
        " first_option": "Arsenal",
        " second_option": "Manchester United",
        " third_option": "Bournemouth",
        " answer": "Bournemouth",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won La Liga in 2003/04?",
        " first_option": "Real madrid",
        " second_option": "Barcelona",
        " third_option": "Valencia",
        " answer": "Valencia",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was top scorer at 2018 World Cup?",
        " first_option": "Mario Gotze",
        " second_option": "Robert Lewandoski",
        " third_option": "Harry Kane",
        " answer": "Harry Kane",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brendan Rodgers managed which club before joining Celtic ?",
        " first_option": "South Hampton",
        " second_option": "Everton",
        " third_option": "Liverpool",
        " answer": "Liverpool",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Arsene Wenger managed which premier league club?",
        " first_option": "Everton",
        " second_option": "Chelsea ",
        " third_option": "Arsenal",
        " answer": "Arsenal",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these players has NOT won the Balon D\u2019or?",
        " first_option": "Kaka",
        " second_option": "Micheal Owen ",
        " third_option": "Thierry Henry",
        " answer": "Thierry Henry",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Samuel Eto\u2019o played for Chelsea and what other English club?",
        " first_option": "West Ham",
        " second_option": "Arsenal",
        " third_option": "Everton",
        " answer": "Everton",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won the 2004 Euro ?",
        " first_option": "Germany",
        " second_option": "Spain",
        " third_option": "Czech Republic",
        " answer": "Czech Republic",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which number did Ronaldinho wear for AC Milan?",
        " first_option": "80",
        " second_option": "99",
        " third_option": "10",
        " answer": "80",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was top scorer in the 2012/13 serie a?",
        " first_option": "Edinson Cavani",
        " second_option": "Kenny Dalgish",
        " third_option": "Kylian Mbappe",
        " answer": "Edinson Cavani",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country hosted the 1994 World Cup?",
        " first_option": "USA",
        " second_option": "France",
        " third_option": "Brazil",
        " answer": "USA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many goals did Wayne Rooney score on his Manchester Utd debut?",
        " first_option": "3",
        " second_option": "0",
        " third_option": "2",
        " answer": "3",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who finished runner up in the 2007 Champions League Final?",
        " first_option": "Liverpool",
        " second_option": "Chelsea ",
        " third_option": "Manchester United",
        " answer": "Liverpool",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these teams has won the most league titles?",
        " first_option": "Real Madrid",
        " second_option": "Celtic",
        " third_option": "Manchester united",
        " answer": "Celtic",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which German club won the 1997 Champions League?",
        " first_option": "Wolfsburg",
        " second_option": "Borussia Dortmund",
        " third_option": "Bayern Munich",
        " answer": "Borussia Dortmund",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who did Manchester Utd beat in the 1999 Champions League Final?",
        " first_option": "Real Madrid",
        " second_option": "Bayern Munich",
        " third_option": "AC milan",
        " answer": "Bayern Munich",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Javier Zanetti played for which Italian club?",
        " first_option": "Lille",
        " second_option": "Inter  Milan",
        " third_option": "Roma",
        " answer": "Inter  Milan",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these teams have never been relegated from the premier league?",
        " first_option": "Manchester United",
        " second_option": "Liverpool",
        " third_option": "Chelsea",
        " answer": "Liverpool",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jordan Henderson joined Liverpool from Sunderland in what year?",
        " first_option": "2013",
        " second_option": "2011",
        " third_option": "2010",
        " answer": "2011",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What club did Luis Suarez join liverpool from in 2011 ?",
        " first_option": "Barcelona ",
        " second_option": "Ajax",
        " third_option": "Athletico Madrid",
        " answer": "Ajax",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Birmingham City, Stoke City, Sunderland play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Spain",
        " second_option": "England",
        " third_option": "Italy",
        " answer": "England",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Chievo, Livorno, Udinese play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "England",
        " second_option": "Italy",
        " third_option": "Spain",
        " answer": "Italy",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Real Sociedad, Osasuna, Mallorca play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "England",
        " second_option": "Spain",
        " third_option": "Italy",
        " answer": "Spain",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Central Coast Mariners, Newcastle Jets, Gold Coast United play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Wales",
        " second_option": "Australia",
        " third_option": "England",
        " answer": "Australia",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "FSV Mainz 05, VfL Bochum, SC Freiburg play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Italy",
        " second_option": "Germany",
        " third_option": "France",
        " answer": "Germany",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "St. Mirren, Aberdeen, Dundee United play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "England",
        " second_option": "Scotland",
        " third_option": "Wales",
        " answer": "Scotland",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sanfrecce Hiroshima, Yokohama F. Marinos, Kashima Antlers play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Thailand",
        " second_option": "Japan",
        " third_option": "China",
        " answer": "Japan",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "FC Lorient, Montpellier HSC, Valenciennes play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "England",
        " second_option": "France",
        " third_option": "Sweden",
        " answer": "France",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shamrock Rovers, Bohemians, Bray Wanderers play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Wales",
        " second_option": "Ireland",
        " third_option": "England",
        " answer": "Ireland",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "V\u00e9lez S\u00e1rsfield, Rosario Central, Boca Juniors play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Brazil",
        " second_option": "Argentina",
        " third_option": "Peru",
        " answer": "Argentina",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "IF Elfsborg, \u00d6rgryte IS, Malm\u00f6 FF play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Austria",
        " second_option": "Sweden",
        " third_option": "Wales",
        " answer": "Sweden",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Orlando Pirates, Kaizer Chiefs, Mamelodi Sundowns play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Uganda",
        " second_option": "South Africa",
        " third_option": "Zambia",
        " answer": "South Africa",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "ADO Den Haag, Groningen, Heerenveen play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Sweden",
        " second_option": "Netherlands",
        " third_option": "Germany",
        " answer": "Netherlands",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Braga, Benfica, Mar\u00edtimo play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Netherlands",
        " second_option": "Portugal",
        " third_option": "Spain",
        " answer": "Portugal",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Viktoria Plze\u0148, Vyso\u010dina Jihlava, Zbrojovka Brno play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Turkey",
        " second_option": "Czech Republic",
        " third_option": "Spain",
        " answer": "Czech Republic",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Seattle Sounders, Columbus Crew, Colorado Rapids play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Canada",
        " second_option": "United States",
        " third_option": "Jamaica",
        " answer": "United States",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vasco da Gama, Fluminense, Palmeirasplay in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Argentina",
        " second_option": "Brazil",
        " third_option": "Peru",
        " answer": "Brazil",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Am\u00e9rica, Santos Laguna, Cruz Azul play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Brazil",
        " second_option": "Mexico",
        " third_option": "United States",
        " answer": "Mexico",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Olympiacos, Aris Thessaloniki, Atromitos play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Sweden",
        " second_option": "Greece",
        " third_option": "Turkey",
        " answer": "Greece",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Zamalek, Al Ahly, Haras El Hedoodplay in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Nigeria",
        " second_option": "Egypt",
        " third_option": "Morroco",
        " answer": "Egypt",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Enyimba, Kano Pillars, MFM united play in which country ?",
        " first_option": "Ghana",
        " second_option": "Nigeria",
        " third_option": "Benin",
        " answer": "Nigeria",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has won the most champions leagues?",
        " first_option": "Liverpool",
        " second_option": "Real Madrid",
        " third_option": "AC milan",
        " answer": "Real Madrid",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Argentina Won the World cup in which of these years?",
        " first_option": "1974",
        " second_option": "1978",
        " third_option": "1982",
        " answer": "1978",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many teams qualify for the World Cup?",
        " first_option": "24",
        " second_option": "32",
        " third_option": "40",
        " answer": "32",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many years is the World cup run?",
        " first_option": "Every 2 years",
        " second_option": "Every 4 years",
        " third_option": "Every 6 years",
        " answer": "Every 4 years",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won the first World cup?",
        " first_option": "Brazil",
        " second_option": "Uruguay",
        " third_option": "Spain",
        " answer": "Uruguay",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did England win the World Cup?",
        " first_option": "1952",
        " second_option": "1956",
        " third_option": "1954",
        " answer": "1956",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times did Liverpool win the European Cup/UEFA Champions League?",
        " first_option": "6",
        " second_option": "5",
        " third_option": "7",
        " answer": "5",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was the World Cup held in 1986?",
        " first_option": "United states",
        " second_option": "Mexico",
        " third_option": "Italy",
        " answer": "Mexico",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has won the most English FA Cups?",
        " first_option": "Liverpool",
        " second_option": "Manchester United",
        " third_option": "Chelsea",
        " answer": "Manchester United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has won the most World Cups?",
        " first_option": "Germany",
        " second_option": "Brazil",
        " third_option": "Italy",
        " answer": "Brazil",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has won the most league titles in top flight English football?",
        " first_option": "Liverpool",
        " second_option": "Manchester United",
        " third_option": "Arsenal",
        " answer": "Manchester United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which football club has won most Spanish league titles?",
        " first_option": "Valencia",
        " second_option": "Real Madrid",
        " third_option": "Barcelona",
        " answer": "Real Madrid",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has scored the most goals in World cup history?",
        " first_option": "Pele",
        " second_option": "Ronaldo Nazario de Lima",
        " third_option": "Johan Cryuff",
        " answer": "Ronaldo Nazario de Lima",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these players have won the most World Cups?",
        " first_option": "Maradona",
        " second_option": "Pele",
        " third_option": "Ronaldinho",
        " answer": "Pele",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Highest number of World cups won by a team?",
        " first_option": "3",
        " second_option": "4",
        " third_option": "5",
        " answer": "5",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which club did Delima Ronaldo join first when he was a kid?",
        " first_option": "Santos",
        " second_option": "Andorinha",
        " third_option": "Fluminese",
        " answer": "Andorinha",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is St James' Park?",
        " first_option": "Crystal Palace",
        " second_option": "Newcastle United",
        " third_option": "Arsenal",
        " answer": "Newcastle United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Selhurst Park?",
        " first_option": "Newcastle United",
        " second_option": "Crystal Palace",
        " third_option": "Arsenal",
        " answer": "Crystal Palace",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Emirates Stadium?",
        " first_option": "Everton",
        " second_option": "Arsenal",
        " third_option": "Newcastle United",
        " answer": "Arsenal",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Goodison Park?",
        " first_option": "WIgan Athletic",
        " second_option": "Everton",
        " third_option": "Arsenal",
        " answer": "Everton",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is DW Stadium?",
        " first_option": "Middlesbrough",
        " second_option": "Wigan Athletic",
        " third_option": "QPR",
        " answer": "Wigan Athletic",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Riverside Stadium?",
        " first_option": "West Ham United",
        " second_option": "Middlesbrough",
        " third_option": "QPR",
        " answer": "Middlesbrough",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Boleyn Ground?",
        " first_option": "Middlesbrough",
        " second_option": "West Ham United",
        " third_option": "QPR",
        " answer": "West Ham United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Loftus Road?",
        " first_option": "Middlesbrough",
        " second_option": "QPR",
        " third_option": "West Ham United",
        " answer": "QPR",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Carrow Road?",
        " first_option": "WIgan Athletic",
        " second_option": "Norwich City F.C.",
        " third_option": "QPR",
        " answer": "Norwich City F.C.",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Reebok Stadium?",
        " first_option": "Norwich City F.C.",
        " second_option": "Bolton Wanderers",
        " third_option": "QPR",
        " answer": "Bolton Wanderers",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Tottenham Hotspur Stadium?",
        " first_option": "Norwich City F.C.",
        " second_option": "Tottenham Hotspur",
        " third_option": "Manchester United",
        " answer": "Tottenham Hotspur",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Old Trafford?",
        " first_option": "Sheffield United",
        " second_option": "Manchester United",
        " third_option": "Tottenham Hotspur",
        " answer": "Manchester United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Bramall Lane?",
        " first_option": "Tottenham Hotspur",
        " second_option": "Manchester United",
        " third_option": "Sheffield United",
        " answer": "Sheffield United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Anfield?",
        " first_option": "Manchester united",
        " second_option": "Sheffield United",
        " third_option": "Liverpool",
        " answer": "Liverpool",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Craven Cottage?",
        " first_option": "Manchester City",
        " second_option": "Sunderland",
        " third_option": "Fulham",
        " answer": "Fulham",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Etihad Stadium?",
        " first_option": "Fulham",
        " second_option": "Sheffield United",
        " third_option": "Manchester City",
        " answer": "Manchester City",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Stadium of Light?",
        " first_option": "Arsenal",
        " second_option": "Leeds United",
        " third_option": "Sunderland",
        " answer": "Sunderland",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Elland Road?",
        " first_option": "Sheffield Wednesday",
        " second_option": "Millwall",
        " third_option": "Leeds United",
        " answer": "Leeds United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is The New Den?",
        " first_option": "Sheffield Wednesday",
        " second_option": "Leeds United",
        " third_option": "Millwall",
        " answer": "Millwall",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Hillsborough?",
        " first_option": "Leeds United",
        " second_option": "Millwall",
        " third_option": "Sheffield Wednesday",
        " answer": "Sheffield Wednesday",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is Turf Moor?",
        " first_option": "Sheffield Wednesday",
        " second_option": "Millwall",
        " third_option": "Burnley",
        " answer": "Burnley",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's home ground is The Valley?",
        " first_option": "Sheffield Wednesday",
        " second_option": "Burnley",
        " third_option": "Charlton Athletic",
        " answer": "Charlton Athletic",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these coaches won the 2010 UEFA Champions League final with Inter Milan ?",
        " first_option": "Claudio Ranieri",
        " second_option": "Massimiliano Allegri",
        " third_option": "Jose Mourinho",
        " answer": "Jose Mourinho",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these coaches won the 2011 UEFA Champions League final with Barcelona ?",
        " first_option": "Claudio Ranieri",
        " second_option": "Jose Mourinho",
        " third_option": "Pep Guardiola",
        " answer": "Pep Guardiola",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these coaches won the 2012 UEFA Champions League final with Chelsea ?",
        " first_option": "Claudio Ranieri",
        " second_option": "Pep Guardiola",
        " third_option": "Roberto Di Matteo",
        " answer": "Roberto Di Matteo",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these coaches won the 2013 UEFA Champions League final with Bayern Munich ?",
        " first_option": "Pep Guardiola",
        " second_option": "Jose Mourinho",
        " third_option": "Jupp Heynckes",
        " answer": "Jupp Heynckes",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these coaches won the 2014 UEFA Champions League final with Real Madrid ?",
        " first_option": "Jupp Heynckes",
        " second_option": "Luis Henrique",
        " third_option": "Carlo Ancelotti",
        " answer": "Carlo Ancelotti",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these coaches won the 2015 UEFA Champions League final with Barcelona?",
        " first_option": "Jupp Heynckes",
        " second_option": "Jose Mourinho",
        " third_option": "Luis Henrique",
        " answer": "Luis Henrique",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these coaches won the 2016 UEFA Champions League final with Real Madrid ?",
        " first_option": "Jupp Heynckes",
        " second_option": "Luis Henrique",
        " third_option": "Zinedine Zidane",
        " answer": "Zinedine Zidane",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these coaches won the 2017 UEFA Champions League final with Real Madrid ?",
        " first_option": "Jupp Heynckes",
        " second_option": "Luis Henrique",
        " third_option": "Zinedine Zidane",
        " answer": "Zinedine Zidane",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these coaches won the 2018 UEFA Champions League final with Real Madrid ?",
        " first_option": "Claudio Ranieri",
        " second_option": "Luis Henrique",
        " third_option": "Zinedine Zidane",
        " answer": "Zinedine Zidane",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these coaches won the 2019 UEFA Champions League final with Liverpool ?",
        " first_option": "Claudio Ranieri",
        " second_option": "Carlo Ancelotti",
        " third_option": "Jurgen Klopp",
        " answer": "Jurgen Klopp",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The stadium lights up red when Bayern Munich play. What is the name of this stadium?",
        " first_option": "Stade de Gerland",
        " second_option": "Stadio Olimpico",
        " third_option": "Allianz Arena",
        " answer": "Allianz Arena",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "this stadium is the home of Olympique Lyonnais, What is the name of the stadium ?",
        " first_option": "Allianz Arena",
        " second_option": "Stadio Olimpico",
        " third_option": "Stade de Gerland",
        " answer": "Stade de Gerland",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "This big football stadium is the home of F.C Barcelona. Which stadium in Europe am I?",
        " first_option": "Nou stadio",
        " second_option": "Camp Marca",
        " third_option": "Camp Nou",
        " answer": "Camp Nou",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "I've decided to take a trip to the Santiago Bernabeu. Which team is home to the Bernabeu?",
        " first_option": "Athletico Madrid",
        " second_option": "Udinese",
        " third_option": "Real Madrid",
        " answer": "Real Madrid",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Italy is home to the legendary stadium San Siro. Which two teams play here?",
        " first_option": "AC milan & Roma",
        " second_option": "Inter Milan &  Udinese ",
        " third_option": "Inter Milan & AC Milan",
        " answer": "Inter Milan & AC Milan",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The largest stadium in Rome is ?",
        " first_option": "San Siro",
        " second_option": "Allianz Arena",
        " third_option": "Stadio Olimpico",
        " answer": "Stadio Olimpico",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Estadio do Dragao is home to which of these Portugal team?",
        " first_option": "Slavia Prague",
        " second_option": "Benefica ",
        " third_option": "FC Porto",
        " answer": "FC Porto",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anfield was home to which other team other than Liverpool ?",
        " first_option": "Portsmouth",
        " second_option": "Reading",
        " third_option": "Everton",
        " answer": "Everton",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Stadio Olimpico is home to how many teams  ?",
        " first_option": "3",
        " second_option": "1",
        " third_option": "2",
        " answer": "2",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these two teams share Stadio Olimpico as their Home ground ?",
        " first_option": "Inter Milan & AC Milan",
        " second_option": "Cesena & Massimo",
        " third_option": "A.S Roma & S.S Napoli",
        " answer": "A.S Roma & S.S Napoli",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which national side play at The Azteca?",
        " first_option": "Uruguay",
        " second_option": "Peru",
        " third_option": "Mexico",
        " answer": "Mexico",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do England's Wolverhampton Wanderers play their home matches?",
        " first_option": "Craven Cottage",
        " second_option": "Signal Iduna",
        " third_option": "Molineux",
        " answer": "Molineux",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Where would you find the Ullevi stadium?",
        " first_option": "Russia",
        " second_option": "Ukraine",
        " third_option": "Sweden",
        " answer": "Sweden",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which French side play at Stade Louis II?",
        " first_option": "London",
        " second_option": "Rome",
        " third_option": "Monaco",
        " answer": "Monaco",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city would you find the Stadio Delle Alpi?",
        " first_option": "Madrid",
        " second_option": "Paris",
        " third_option": "Turin",
        " answer": "Turin",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which French Stadium hosted the 1998 World Cup Final between France and Brazil?",
        " first_option": "Stadio francais",
        " second_option": "Stade Louis II",
        " third_option": "Stade de France",
        " answer": "Stade de France",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many people were reputedly inside Brazil's Maracana Stadium for the 1950 World Cup Final?",
        " first_option": "100,000",
        " second_option": "50,000",
        " third_option": "200,000",
        " answer": "200,000",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name Iran's stadium?",
        " first_option": " Al Mawsil Stadium",
        " second_option": "Al kibah Stadium",
        " third_option": "Azadi Stadium",
        " answer": "Azadi Stadium",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The \"Theatre of Dreams\" is better known as what?",
        " first_option": "Anfield",
        " second_option": "Goodison Park",
        " third_option": "Old Trafford",
        " answer": "Old Trafford",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The English national soccer team play all their home games in which stadium?",
        " first_option": "Anfield",
        " second_option": "Old Trafford",
        " third_option": "Wembley Stadium",
        " answer": "Wembley Stadium",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the club where Brazilian striker Pele became an idol?",
        " first_option": "Boca Juniors",
        " second_option": "River Plate",
        " third_option": "Santos",
        " answer": "Santos",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the Italian club where striker Marco Van Basten became an idol?",
        " first_option": "Udinese",
        " second_option": "Inter Milan",
        " third_option": "AC Milan",
        " answer": "AC Milan",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which are the clubs where striker Johan Cruyff became an idol?",
        " first_option": "Arsenal, Barcelona",
        " second_option": "Arsenal, Bayern Munich",
        " third_option": "Ajax, Barcelona",
        " answer": "Ajax, Barcelona",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the club where striker Gerd Muller became an idol?",
        " first_option": "Arsenal",
        " second_option": "Bayern Munich",
        " third_option": "AC milan",
        " answer": "Bayern Munich",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the club where Argentinian player Diego Armando Maradona became an idol?",
        " first_option": "Inter Milan",
        " second_option": "Napoli",
        " third_option": "Roma",
        " answer": "Napoli",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the club where Kenny Dalglish became an idol?",
        " first_option": "Chelsea ",
        " second_option": "Liverpool",
        " third_option": "Barcelona",
        " answer": "Liverpool",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the club where French player Zinedine Zidane is really an idol?",
        " first_option": "Liverpool",
        " second_option": "Juventus",
        " third_option": "Inter  Milan",
        " answer": "Juventus",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the club where Uruguayan player Enzo Francescoli became an idol?",
        " first_option": "Valencia",
        " second_option": "River Plate",
        " third_option": "Boca Juniors",
        " answer": "River Plate",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the club where Bulgarian player Hristo Stoichkov became an idol?",
        " first_option": "Inter Milan",
        " second_option": "F.C. Barcelona",
        " third_option": "Arsenal",
        " answer": "F.C. Barcelona",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the club where Bobby Charlton became an idol?",
        " first_option": "Chelsea",
        " second_option": "Manchester United",
        " third_option": "Arsenal",
        " answer": "Manchester United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which are the clubs where Luis Suarez became an idol?",
        " first_option": "Sporting Lisbon, Bilbao",
        " second_option": "Porto, Athletico Madrid ",
        " third_option": "AJax, Madrid",
        " answer": "Porto, Athletico Madrid ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the club where defender Franco Baresi became an idol?",
        " first_option": "Roma",
        " second_option": "AC Milan",
        " third_option": "Juventus",
        " answer": "AC Milan",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the club where defender Frank Lampard became an idol?",
        " first_option": "AC Milan",
        " second_option": "Chelsea",
        " third_option": "Manchester City",
        " answer": "Chelsea",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the club where Ronaldinho became an idol?",
        " first_option": "Bayern Munich",
        " second_option": "F.C. Barcelona",
        " third_option": "Lyon",
        " answer": "F.C. Barcelona",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the club where Lionel Messi became an idol?",
        " first_option": "Bayern Munich",
        " second_option": "F.C. Barcelona",
        " third_option": "Arsenal",
        " answer": "F.C. Barcelona",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the club where Alvaro Recoba became an idol?",
        " first_option": "Real Madrid",
        " second_option": "Inter Milan",
        " third_option": "Sevilla",
        " answer": "Inter Milan",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the club where Wayne Rooney became an idol?",
        " first_option": "Manchester City",
        " second_option": "Manchester United",
        " third_option": "Portsmouth",
        " answer": "Manchester United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the club where Thierry Henry became an idol?",
        " first_option": "Manchester United",
        " second_option": "Arsenal",
        " third_option": "Juventus",
        " answer": "Arsenal",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is these teams is referred to as the OLD LADY ?",
        " first_option": "Manchester United",
        " second_option": "Juventus",
        " third_option": "Chelsea",
        " answer": "Juventus",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In 2003-04, who became the new owner of \"Chelsea\"?",
        " first_option": "Malcolm Glazier",
        " second_option": "Roman Abramovich",
        " third_option": "Ivan Abramovich",
        " answer": "Roman Abramovich",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owns Liverpool ?",
        " first_option": "YNWA",
        " second_option": "Fenway Sports Group",
        " third_option": "Rocafela",
        " answer": "Fenway Sports Group",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "During the 2004-2005 season, which team ended Arsenal's streak of 49 matches without defeat?",
        " first_option": "Mancchester City",
        " second_option": "Manchester United",
        " third_option": "Newcastle United ",
        " answer": "Manchester United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owns Chelsea ?",
        " first_option": "Ivan Abramovich",
        " second_option": "Roman Abramovich",
        " third_option": "Malcolm Glazier",
        " answer": "Roman Abramovich",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owns Manchester United ?",
        " first_option": "Roman Abramovich",
        " second_option": "The Glazer Family",
        " third_option": "Enzo Francescoli",
        " answer": "The Glazer Family",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owns Arsenal ?",
        " first_option": "The Glazer Family",
        " second_option": "Stan Kroenke",
        " third_option": "Roman Abramovich",
        " answer": "Stan Kroenke",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did Dennis Bergkamp join \"Arsenal\"?",
        " first_option": "1994",
        " second_option": "1995",
        " third_option": "1996",
        " answer": "1995",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Arsenal \"bought\" Thierry Henry in 1999 from which team?",
        " first_option": "Milan",
        " second_option": "Juventus",
        " third_option": "Lyon",
        " answer": "Juventus",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owns Tottenham Hotspur ?",
        " first_option": "Florentino Perez",
        " second_option": "Joe Lewis",
        " third_option": "Zhan Jindang",
        " answer": "Joe Lewis",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owns Inter Milan ?",
        " first_option": "Florentino Perez",
        " second_option": "Zhan Jindang",
        " third_option": "Shahid Khan",
        " answer": "Zhan Jindang",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owns Fulham ?",
        " first_option": "Florentino Perez",
        " second_option": "Shahid Khan",
        " third_option": "Zhan Jindang",
        " answer": "Shahid Khan",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owns Juventus ?",
        " first_option": "The Angelli Family",
        " second_option": "Florentino Perez",
        " third_option": "Sheikh Mansour",
        " answer": "The Angelli Family",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owns Manchester City?",
        " first_option": "Sheikh Mansour",
        " second_option": "Florentino Perez",
        " third_option": "The Angelli Family",
        " answer": "Sheikh Mansour",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owns Barcelona?",
        " first_option": "Club Members",
        " second_option": "Florentino Perez",
        " third_option": "Kunle Soname",
        " answer": "Club Members",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owns Real Madrid ?",
        " first_option": "Florentino Perez",
        " second_option": "Kunle Soname",
        " third_option": "Club Members",
        " answer": "Florentino Perez",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owns Clube Desportivo Feirense?",
        " first_option": "Kunle Soname",
        " second_option": "Chris Giwa",
        " third_option": "Club Members",
        " answer": "Kunle Soname",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owns FC IfeanyiUbah?",
        " first_option": "Ifeanyi Ubah",
        " second_option": "Chris Giwa",
        " third_option": "Kevin Phillips",
        " answer": "Ifeanyi Ubah",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owns Giwa Fc?",
        " first_option": "Chris Giwa",
        " second_option": "Kevin Phillips",
        " third_option": "Ifeanyi Ubah",
        " answer": "Chris Giwa",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owns ABS FC?",
        " first_option": "Bukola Saraki",
        " second_option": "Chris Giwa",
        " third_option": "Ifeanyi Ubah",
        " answer": "Bukola Saraki",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owns Remo Stars?",
        " first_option": "Kunle Soname",
        " second_option": "Chris Giwa",
        " third_option": "Ifeanyi Ubah",
        " answer": "Kunle Soname",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the soccer legend ?",
        " first_option": "Peter Schmeichel",
        " second_option": "Dino Zoff",
        " third_option": "Oliver Kahn",
        " answer": "Peter Schmeichel",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the soccer legend ?",
        " first_option": "Marco Van Basten",
        " second_option": "Ruud Gullit",
        " third_option": "Oliver Kahn",
        " answer": "Marco Van Basten",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the soccer legend ?",
        " first_option": "Eric Cantona",
        " second_option": "Ruud Gullit",
        " third_option": "Dino Zoff",
        " answer": "Eric Cantona",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the soccer legend ?",
        " first_option": "Diego Maradona",
        " second_option": "Ruud Gullit",
        " third_option": "Oliver Kahn",
        " answer": "Diego Maradona",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the soccer legend ?",
        " first_option": "Gary Lineker",
        " second_option": "Diego Maradona",
        " third_option": "Oliver Kahn",
        " answer": "Gary Lineker",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the soccer legend ?",
        " first_option": "Diego Maradona",
        " second_option": "Michel Plantini",
        " third_option": "Florentino Perez",
        " answer": "Michel Plantini",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the soccer legend ?",
        " first_option": "Michel Plantini",
        " second_option": "Johan Cruijff",
        " third_option": "Florentino Perez",
        " answer": "Johan Cruijff",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the soccer legend ?",
        " first_option": "Diego Maradona",
        " second_option": "George Best",
        " third_option": "Florentino Perez",
        " answer": "George Best",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the soccer legend ?",
        " first_option": "Diego Maradona",
        " second_option": "Gabriel Batistuta",
        " third_option": "Florentino Perez",
        " answer": "Gabriel Batistuta",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the soccer legend ?",
        " first_option": "Gabriel Batistuta",
        " second_option": "Pele",
        " third_option": "Florentino Perez",
        " answer": "Pele",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the soccer legend ?",
        " first_option": "Florentino Perez",
        " second_option": "Franz Beckenbauer",
        " third_option": "Diego Maradona",
        " answer": "Franz Beckenbauer",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did the Premier League start?",
        " first_option": "1994",
        " second_option": "1992",
        " third_option": "1996",
        " answer": "1992",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first sponsor of the Premier League?",
        " first_option": "BBC",
        " second_option": "Carling",
        " third_option": "Barclays",
        " answer": "Carling",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In what season did Roman Abramovich take over Chelsea?",
        " first_option": "2005/06",
        " second_option": "2003/04",
        " third_option": "2004/05",
        " answer": "2003/04",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which player holds the record for the most goals in consecutive Premier League games?",
        " first_option": "Thierry Henry",
        " second_option": "Jamie Vardy",
        " third_option": "Sergio Aguero",
        " answer": "Jamie Vardy",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kevin Phillips won the Golden Boot in 1999/2000, who was the next English player to do so?",
        " first_option": "Jamie Defoe",
        " second_option": "Harry Kane",
        " third_option": "Alan Shearer",
        " answer": "Harry Kane",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who scored the first \u2018perfect hat-trick\u2019 (left foot, right foot, and header) in the Premier League?",
        " first_option": "Thierry Henry",
        " second_option": "Jimmy Floyd Hasselbaink",
        " third_option": "Sergio Aguero",
        " answer": "Jimmy Floyd Hasselbaink",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What player scored four goals in 12 minutes after coming on as a sub versus Nottingham Forest?",
        " first_option": "Thierry Henry",
        " second_option": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
        " third_option": "Darren Bent",
        " answer": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which goalkeeper has the record of 138 clean sheets for the same Premier League team?",
        " first_option": "Peter Schmeichel",
        " second_option": "Petr Cech ",
        " third_option": "Edwin Van der Sar",
        " answer": "Petr Cech ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many clubs have never been relegated from the Premier League?",
        " first_option": "Four",
        " second_option": "Six",
        " third_option": "Five ",
        " answer": "Six",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many teams were in the first ever Premier League?",
        " first_option": "21",
        " second_option": "22",
        " third_option": "23",
        " answer": "22",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two non-English clubs have played in the Premier League?",
        " first_option": "Celtic & Rangers",
        " second_option": "Swansea & Cardiff City",
        " third_option": "Aberdeen & Wimbeldon",
        " answer": "Swansea & Cardiff City",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times has the league been renamed?",
        " first_option": "Two",
        " second_option": "Four",
        " third_option": "Three ",
        " answer": "Four",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Against which team did Wayne Rooney score his Premier League first goal?",
        " first_option": "Everton",
        " second_option": "Manchester United",
        " third_option": "Arsenal",
        " answer": "Arsenal",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first Premier League manager to be sacked?",
        " first_option": "Roy Hodgson",
        " second_option": "Jose Mourinho",
        " third_option": "Ian Porterfield",
        " answer": "Ian Porterfield",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was Jose Mourinho\u2019s first signing at Chelsea?",
        " first_option": "Didier Drogba",
        " second_option": "Petr Cech ",
        " third_option": "Paulo Ferreira",
        " answer": "Paulo Ferreira",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times had David Moyes won the prestigious LMA Manager of the year award?",
        " first_option": "Four",
        " second_option": "Five ",
        " third_option": "Three",
        " answer": "Three",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first Italian manager to win the Premier League?",
        " first_option": "Rafa Benitez",
        " second_option": "Roberto Mancini",
        " third_option": "Carlo Ancelotti",
        " answer": "Carlo Ancelotti",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which manager was in charge at Manchester City when they won their first Premier League title?",
        " first_option": "Carlo Ancelotti",
        " second_option": "Michel Pellegrini",
        " third_option": "Roberto Mancini",
        " answer": "Roberto Mancini",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has managed Reading, Swansea and Liverpool?",
        " first_option": "Rafa Benitez",
        " second_option": "Kenny Dalgish",
        " third_option": "Brendan Rodgers",
        " answer": "Brendan Rodgers",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times did Sir Alex Ferguson win the Premier League Manager of the Month award?",
        " first_option": "30",
        " second_option": "25",
        " third_option": "27",
        " answer": "27",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Premier League\u2019s all-time leading goal scorer?",
        " first_option": "Thierry Henry",
        " second_option": "Steven Gerard",
        " third_option": "Alan Sheareer",
        " answer": "Alan Sheareer",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which player holds the record for scoring the most goals in his debut Premier League season?",
        " first_option": "Wayne Rooney",
        " second_option": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        " third_option": "Kevin Phillips",
        " answer": "Kevin Phillips",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who scored the first Premier League hat-trick?",
        " first_option": "Alan Sheareer",
        " second_option": "Gerge Best",
        " third_option": "Eric Cantona",
        " answer": "Eric Cantona",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the player that scored the fastest Premier League hat-trick?",
        " first_option": "Harry Kane",
        " second_option": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        " third_option": "Sadio Mane",
        " answer": "Sadio Mane",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In what season did Arsenal\u2019s \u2018Invincibles\u2019 go the whole season unbeaten?",
        " first_option": "2004/2005",
        " second_option": "2001/02",
        " third_option": "2003/2004",
        " answer": "2003/2004",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won the first Premier League title?",
        " first_option": "Newcastle United",
        " second_option": "Arsenal",
        " third_option": "Manchester United",
        " answer": "Manchester United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times did Alex Ferguson win the Premier League?",
        " first_option": "Eighteen",
        " second_option": "Eight",
        " third_option": "Thirteen",
        " answer": "Thirteen",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            " ",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The winners of the Champions League & the Europe League compete for which trophy?",
        " first_option": "UEFA Champions Trophy",
        " second_option": "UEFA Champions Cup",
        " third_option": "UEFA Super Cup",
        " answer": "UEFA Super Cup",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cLa Liga\u201d is the name of which European country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Germany",
        " second_option": "Italy",
        " third_option": "Spain",
        " answer": "Spain",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cBundesliga\u201d is the name of which European country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Spain",
        " second_option": "Italy",
        " third_option": "Germany",
        " answer": "Germany",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cPremiership\u201d is the name of which European country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Germany",
        " second_option": "Spain",
        " third_option": "England",
        " answer": "England",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cSerie A\u201d is the name of which European country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Germany",
        " second_option": "England",
        " third_option": "italy ",
        " answer": "italy ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cLigue 1\u201d is the name of which European country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Germany",
        " second_option": "England",
        " third_option": "France",
        " answer": "France",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cSuperliga\u201d is the name of which country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Germany",
        " second_option": "France",
        " third_option": "Argentina",
        " answer": "Argentina",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cLiga\u201d is the name of which country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Germany",
        " second_option": "France",
        " third_option": "Austria",
        " answer": "Austria",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cA-League\u201d is the name of which country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Germany",
        " second_option": "Brazil",
        " third_option": "Australia",
        " answer": "Australia",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cPaulista\u201d is the name of which  country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Germany",
        " second_option": "France",
        " third_option": "Brazil",
        " answer": "Brazil",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cHNL\u201d is the name of which European country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Netherlands",
        " second_option": "France",
        " third_option": "Croatia",
        " answer": "Croatia",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cSuperliagen\u201d is the name of which European country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Croatia",
        " second_option": "Netherlands",
        " third_option": "Denmark",
        " answer": "Denmark",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cJ.League\u201d is the name of which country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "China",
        " second_option": "Peru",
        " third_option": "Japan",
        " answer": "Japan",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cPrimiera\u201d is the name of which European country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Italy",
        " second_option": "Spain",
        " third_option": "Portugal",
        " answer": "Portugal",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cEkstraklasa\u201d is the name of which European country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Italy",
        " second_option": "Portugal",
        " third_option": "Poland",
        " answer": "Poland",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cLiga 1\u201d is the name of which European country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Italy",
        " second_option": "Portugal",
        " third_option": "Romania",
        " answer": "Romania",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cChampionship\u201d is the name of which European country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Portugal",
        " second_option": "Romania",
        " third_option": "Scotland",
        " answer": "Scotland",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cSuper League\u201d is the name of which European country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Romania",
        " second_option": "Scotland",
        " third_option": "Switzerland",
        " answer": "Switzerland",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cSuper Lig\u201d is the name of which country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Spain",
        " second_option": "Scotland",
        " third_option": "Turkey",
        " answer": "Turkey",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cMLS\u201d is the name of which country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Roma",
        " second_option": "Scotland",
        " third_option": "Unites States",
        " answer": "Unites States",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cCymru\u201d is the name of which European country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Spain",
        " second_option": "Scotland",
        " third_option": "Wales",
        " answer": "Wales",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cK-League\u201d is the name of which European country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Holland",
        " second_option": "Wales",
        " third_option": "South Korea",
        " answer": "South Korea",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\"First Division\u201d is the name of which European country\u2019s professional football association?",
        " first_option": "Wales",
        " second_option": "Holland",
        " third_option": "Belgium",
        " answer": "Belgium",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Arsenal \" ?",
        " first_option": "Dean Smith",
        " second_option": "Arsene Wenger",
        " third_option": "Mikel Arteta",
        " answer": "Mikel Arteta",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Aston Villa \" ?",
        " first_option": "Mikel Arteta",
        " second_option": "Dean Smith",
        " third_option": "Eddie Howe",
        " answer": "Dean Smith",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"AFC Bournemouth \" ?",
        " first_option": "Dean Smith",
        " second_option": "Eddie Howe",
        " third_option": "Graham Potter",
        " answer": "Eddie Howe",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Brighton & Hove Albion \" ?",
        " first_option": "Dean Smith",
        " second_option": "Graham Potter",
        " third_option": "Eddie Howe",
        " answer": "Graham Potter",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Burnley \" ?",
        " first_option": "Carlo Ancelotti",
        " second_option": "Sean Dyche",
        " third_option": "Eddie Howe",
        " answer": "Sean Dyche",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Chelsea \" ?",
        " first_option": "Sean Dyche",
        " second_option": "Frank Lampard",
        " third_option": "Eddie Howe",
        " answer": "Frank Lampard",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Crystal Palace \" ?",
        " first_option": "Sean Dyche",
        " second_option": "Roy Hodgson",
        " third_option": "Carlo Ancelotti",
        " answer": "Roy Hodgson",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Everton \" ?",
        " first_option": "Sean Dyche",
        " second_option": "Carlo Ancelotti",
        " third_option": "Roy Hodgson",
        " answer": "Carlo Ancelotti",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Leicester City \" ?",
        " first_option": "Carlo Ancelotti",
        " second_option": "Brendan Rogers",
        " third_option": "Roy Hodgson",
        " answer": "Brendan Rogers",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Liverpool \" ?",
        " first_option": "Brendan Rogers",
        " second_option": "Jurgen Klopp",
        " third_option": "Roy Hodgson",
        " answer": "Jurgen Klopp",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Manchester City \" ?",
        " first_option": "Brendan Rogers",
        " second_option": "Pep Guardiola",
        " third_option": "Daniel Farke",
        " answer": "Pep Guardiola",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Mancehster United \" ?",
        " first_option": "Brendan Rogers",
        " second_option": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
        " third_option": "Pep Guardiola",
        " answer": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Newcastle United \" ?",
        " first_option": "Brendan Rogers",
        " second_option": "Steve Bruce",
        " third_option": "Daniel Farke",
        " answer": "Steve Bruce",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Norwich City \" ?",
        " first_option": "Brendan Rogers",
        " second_option": "Daniel Farke",
        " third_option": "Steve Bruce",
        " answer": "Daniel Farke",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Sheffield United \" ?",
        " first_option": "Daniel Farke",
        " second_option": "Chris Wilder",
        " third_option": "Steve Bruce",
        " answer": "Chris Wilder",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Southampton \" ?",
        " first_option": "Sean Dyche",
        " second_option": "Ralph Hasenhuttl",
        " third_option": "Daniel Farke",
        " answer": "Ralph Hasenhuttl",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Tottenham Hotspur \" ?",
        " first_option": "Daniel Farke",
        " second_option": "Jose Mourinho",
        " third_option": "Ralph Hasenhuttl",
        " answer": "Jose Mourinho",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Watford \" ?",
        " first_option": "Dean Smith",
        " second_option": "Nigel Pearson ",
        " third_option": "Ralph Hasenhuttl",
        " answer": "Nigel Pearson ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"West Ham United \" ?",
        " first_option": "Nigel Pearson ",
        " second_option": "David Moyes",
        " third_option": "Ralph Hasenhuttl",
        " answer": "David Moyes",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Wolverhampton Wanderers \" ?",
        " first_option": "Dean Smith",
        " second_option": "Nuno Espirito Santo",
        " third_option": "Nigel Pearson ",
        " answer": "Nuno Espirito Santo",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Atletico Madrid \" ?",
        " first_option": "Zinedine Zidane",
        " second_option": "Diego Simeone",
        " third_option": "Nuno Espirito Santo",
        " answer": "Diego Simeone",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Real Madrid \" ?",
        " first_option": "Nigel Pearson ",
        " second_option": "Zinedine Zidane",
        " third_option": "Nuno Espirito Santo",
        " answer": "Zinedine Zidane",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Barcelona \" ?",
        " first_option": "Zinedine Zidane",
        " second_option": "Quique Setien",
        " third_option": "Nuno Espirito Santo",
        " answer": "Quique Setien",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Sevilla\" ?",
        " first_option": "Zinedine Zidane",
        " second_option": "Julen Lopetegui",
        " third_option": "Gian Piero Gasperini",
        " answer": "Julen Lopetegui",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Atlanta \" ?",
        " first_option": "Zinedine Zidane",
        " second_option": "Julen Lopetegui",
        " third_option": "Gian Piero Gasperini",
        " answer": "Gian Piero Gasperini",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"SS Lazio \" ?",
        " first_option": "Antonio Conte",
        " second_option": "Julen Lopetegui",
        " third_option": "Simeone Inzaghi",
        " answer": "Simeone Inzaghi",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Intermilan\" ?",
        " first_option": "Simeone Inzaghi",
        " second_option": "Julen Lopetegui",
        " third_option": "Antonio Conte",
        " answer": "Antonio Conte",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Juventus \" ?",
        " first_option": "Simeone Inzaghi",
        " second_option": "Antonio Conte",
        " third_option": "Maurizio Sarri",
        " answer": "Maurizio Sarri",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Sampadoria\" ?",
        " first_option": "Antonio Conte",
        " second_option": "Maurizio Sarri",
        " third_option": "Claudio Ranieri",
        " answer": "Claudio Ranieri",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"AC Milan\" ?",
        " first_option": "Claudio Ranieri",
        " second_option": "Niko Kovac",
        " third_option": "Gennaro Gattuso",
        " answer": "Gennaro Gattuso",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Bayern Munich \" ?",
        " first_option": "Claudio Ranieri",
        " second_option": "Gennaro Gattuso",
        " third_option": "Niko Kovac",
        " answer": "Niko Kovac",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Borussia Dortmud\" ?",
        " first_option": "Claudio Ranieri",
        " second_option": "Niko Kovac",
        " third_option": "Lucien Favre",
        " answer": "Lucien Favre",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"RB Leipzig \" ?",
        " first_option": "Niko Kovac",
        " second_option": "Lucien Favre",
        " third_option": "Julian Nagelsmann",
        " answer": "Julian Nagelsmann",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Bayer Leverkusen\" ?",
        " first_option": "Julian Nagelsmann",
        " second_option": "Lucien Favre",
        " third_option": "Peter Bosz",
        " answer": "Peter Bosz",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Borussia Monchengladbach\" ?",
        " first_option": "Peter Bosz",
        " second_option": "Lucien Favre",
        " third_option": "Marco Rose",
        " answer": "Marco Rose",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Nice\" ?",
        " first_option": "Marco Rose",
        " second_option": "Lucien Favre",
        " third_option": "Patrick Vieira",
        " answer": "Patrick Vieira",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Montreal Impact \" ?",
        " first_option": "Marco Rose",
        " second_option": "Patrick Vieira",
        " third_option": "Thierry Henry",
        " answer": "Thierry Henry",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Rangers\" ?",
        " first_option": "Marco Rose",
        " second_option": "Thierry Henry",
        " third_option": "Steven Gerrard",
        " answer": "Steven Gerrard",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Wales \" ?",
        " first_option": "Patrick Vieira",
        " second_option": "Thierry Henry",
        " third_option": "Ryan Giggs",
        " answer": "Ryan Giggs",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the manager of this team \"Ajax amsterdam\" ?",
        " first_option": "Ryan Giggs",
        " second_option": "Thierry Henry",
        " third_option": "Erik ten Hag",
        " answer": "Erik ten Hag",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " FIFA stands for what?",
        " first_option": "Federation of International football associations",
        " second_option": "Football International Federal Assocation ",
        " third_option": "F\u00e9d\u00e9ration Internationale de Football Association",
        " answer": "F\u00e9d\u00e9ration Internationale de Football Association",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the number of players in 1 team of football?",
        " first_option": "12",
        " second_option": "13",
        " third_option": "11",
        " answer": "11",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The FA (Football Association) founded on which year?",
        " first_option": "1861",
        " second_option": "1862",
        " third_option": "1863",
        " answer": "1863",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " In which country the headquarter of FA located?",
        " first_option": "Spain",
        " second_option": "France",
        " third_option": "England",
        " answer": "England",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country won the highest number of World cups?",
        " first_option": "Spain",
        " second_option": "Germany",
        " third_option": "Brazil",
        " answer": "Brazil",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times did Italy win the FIFA World cup?",
        " first_option": "3",
        " second_option": "5",
        " third_option": "4",
        " answer": "4",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many time did Brazil win World cup FIFA?",
        " first_option": "4",
        " second_option": "6",
        " third_option": "5",
        " answer": "5",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times Germany and Brazil played the final FIFA match?",
        " first_option": "6 times",
        " second_option": "8 times",
        " third_option": "7 times",
        " answer": "7 times",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country first FIFA World cup was held?",
        " first_option": "Germany",
        " second_option": "England",
        " third_option": "Uruguay",
        " answer": "Uruguay",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country first FIFA World cup was held which year?",
        " first_option": "1925",
        " second_option": "1935",
        " third_option": "1930",
        " answer": "1930",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won the first football World cup?",
        " first_option": "Germany",
        " second_option": "England",
        " third_option": "Uruguay",
        " answer": "Uruguay",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many football teams have participated in the first football World cup?",
        " first_option": "12",
        " second_option": "14",
        " third_option": "13",
        " answer": "13",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Which team reached in final 3 times but not won the World cup?",
        " first_option": "Spain",
        " second_option": "Germany",
        " third_option": "Holland",
        " answer": "Holland",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which was the first team who won consecutively 2 World cups?",
        " first_option": "Spain",
        " second_option": "Holland",
        " third_option": "Italy ",
        " answer": "Italy ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which player scored more number of goals in FIFA World cup?",
        " first_option": "Thomas Muller",
        " second_option": "Mario Gotze",
        " third_option": "Miroslav Klose",
        " answer": "Miroslav Klose",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the only player who won the World cup 3 times?",
        " first_option": "Franz Beckenbauer",
        " second_option": "Diego Maradona",
        " third_option": "Pele",
        " answer": "Pele",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which football player appeared in the World cup at the age of 43?",
        " first_option": "Fabio Canavarro",
        " second_option": "Javier Matezarri",
        " third_option": "Faryd Mondragon",
        " answer": "Faryd Mondragon",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "which is the youngest player appeared in the World cup?",
        " first_option": "Faryd Mondragon",
        " second_option": "Javier Matezarri",
        " third_option": "Norman Whiteside",
        " answer": "Norman Whiteside",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who played the maximum number of World cup matches?",
        " first_option": "Faryd Mondragon",
        " second_option": "Norman Whiteside",
        " third_option": "Lothar Matthaus",
        " answer": "Lothar Matthaus",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The oldest player appeared in the World cup final was?",
        " first_option": "Norman Whiteside",
        " second_option": "Lothar Matthaus",
        " third_option": "Dino Zoff",
        " answer": "Dino Zoff",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The first man to score a goal in 4 different FA finals?",
        " first_option": "Dino Zoff",
        " second_option": "Lothar Matthaus",
        " third_option": "Didier Drogba",
        " answer": "Didier Drogba",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "AFG is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Andorra",
        " second_option": "Angola",
        " third_option": "Afghanistan",
        " answer": "Afghanistan",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "AND is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Andorra",
        " second_option": "Angola",
        " third_option": "Andorra",
        " answer": "Andorra",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "ALB is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Andorra",
        " second_option": "Angola",
        " third_option": "Albania",
        " answer": "Albania",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "ALG is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Albania",
        " second_option": "Angola",
        " third_option": "Algeria",
        " answer": "Algeria",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "ASA is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Albania",
        " second_option": "Algeria",
        " third_option": "American Samoa",
        " answer": "American Samoa",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "ANG is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Algeria",
        " second_option": "American Samoa",
        " third_option": "Angola",
        " answer": "Angola",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "AIA is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Angola",
        " second_option": "American Samoa",
        " third_option": "Anguilla",
        " answer": "Anguilla",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "ATG is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Argentina",
        " second_option": "American Samoa",
        " third_option": "Antigua & Barbuda",
        " answer": "Antigua & Barbuda",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "ARG is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Antigua & Barbuda",
        " second_option": "American Samoa",
        " third_option": "Argentina",
        " answer": "Argentina",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "ARM is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Antigua & Barbuda",
        " second_option": "Argentina",
        " third_option": "Armenia",
        " answer": "Armenia",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "ARU is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Argentina",
        " second_option": "Australia",
        " third_option": "Aruba",
        " answer": "Aruba",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "AUS is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Aruba",
        " second_option": "Austria",
        " third_option": "Australia",
        " answer": "Australia",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "AUT is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Aruba",
        " second_option": "Australia",
        " third_option": "Austria",
        " answer": "Austria",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "AZE is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Austria",
        " second_option": "Australia",
        " third_option": "Azerbaijan",
        " answer": "Azerbaijan",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "BAH is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Azerbaijan",
        " second_option": "Austria",
        " third_option": "Bahamas",
        " answer": "Bahamas",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "BHR is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Azerbaijan",
        " second_option": "Bahamas",
        " third_option": "Bahrain",
        " answer": "Bahrain",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "BAN is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Bahrain",
        " second_option": "Bahamas",
        " third_option": "Bangladesh",
        " answer": "Bangladesh",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "BRB is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Barbados",
        " second_option": "Bangladesh",
        " third_option": "Bahamas",
        " answer": "Barbados",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "BLR is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "Belarus",
        " second_option": "Bangladesh",
        " third_option": "Barbados",
        " answer": "Belarus",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "BEL is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "BELGIUM",
        " second_option": "BELIZE",
        " third_option": "BELARUS",
        " answer": "BELGIUM",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "BLZ is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "BELIZE",
        " second_option": "BELGIUM",
        " third_option": "BELARUS",
        " answer": "BELIZE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "BEN is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "BENIN",
        " second_option": "BELIZE",
        " third_option": "BELARUS",
        " answer": "BENIN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "BER is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "BERMUDA",
        " second_option": "BELIZE",
        " third_option": "BENIN",
        " answer": "BERMUDA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "BHU is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "BHUTAN",
        " second_option": "BENIN",
        " third_option": "BERMUDA",
        " answer": "BHUTAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "BOL is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "BOLIVIA",
        " second_option": "BHUTAN",
        " third_option": "BERMUDA",
        " answer": "BOLIVIA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "BIH is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "BOSNIA & HERZEGONIA",
        " second_option": "BHUTAN",
        " third_option": "BRAZIL",
        " answer": "BOSNIA & HERZEGONIA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "BRA is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "BRAZIL",
        " second_option": "BHUTAN",
        " third_option": "BOSNIA & HERZEGONIA",
        " answer": "BRAZIL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "VGB is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "BIRTISH VIRGIN ISLANDS",
        " second_option": "BRAZIL",
        " third_option": "BOSNIA & HERZEGONIA",
        " answer": "BIRTISH VIRGIN ISLANDS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "BRU is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "BRUNEI",
        " second_option": "BIRTISH VIRGIN ISLANDS",
        " third_option": "BOSNIA & HERZEGONIA",
        " answer": "BRUNEI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "BFA is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "BURKINA FASO",
        " second_option": "BIRTISH VIRGIN ISLANDS",
        " third_option": "BRUNEI",
        " answer": "BURKINA FASO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "BDI is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "BURUNDI",
        " second_option": "BIRTISH VIRGIN ISLANDS",
        " third_option": "BURKINA FASO",
        " answer": "BURUNDI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "CAM is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "CAMBODIA",
        " second_option": "CAMEROON",
        " third_option": "BURKINA FASO",
        " answer": "CAMBODIA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "CMR is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "CAMEROON",
        " second_option": "CAMBODIA",
        " third_option": "BURKINA FASO",
        " answer": "CAMEROON",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "CAN is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "CANADA",
        " second_option": "CAMBODIA",
        " third_option": "CAMEROON",
        " answer": "CANADA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "CPV is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "CAPE VERDE",
        " second_option": "CAMEROON",
        " third_option": "CANADA",
        " answer": "CAPE VERDE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "CAY is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "CAYMAN ISLAND",
        " second_option": "CAPE VERDE",
        " third_option": "CANADA",
        " answer": "CAYMAN ISLAND",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "CTA is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "CENTRAL AFRICAN REPUBLIC",
        " second_option": "CAPE VERDE",
        " third_option": "CAYMAN ISLAND",
        " answer": "CENTRAL AFRICAN REPUBLIC",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "CHI is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "CHILE",
        " second_option": "CAPE VERDE",
        " third_option": "CENTRAL AFRICAN REPUBLIC",
        " answer": "CHILE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "CHN is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "CHINA PR",
        " second_option": "CHILE",
        " third_option": "CENTRAL AFRICAN REPUBLIC",
        " answer": "CHINA PR",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "TPE is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "CHINESE TAIPEI",
        " second_option": "CHINA PR",
        " third_option": "CHILE",
        " answer": "CHINESE TAIPEI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "COL is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "COLOMBIA",
        " second_option": "CHINA PR",
        " third_option": "CHINESE TAIPEI",
        " answer": "COLOMBIA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "COM is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "COMOROS",
        " second_option": "CONGO DR",
        " third_option": "CHINESE TAIPEI",
        " answer": "COMOROS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "COD is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "CONGO DR",
        " second_option": "COMOROS",
        " third_option": "CHINESE TAIPEI",
        " answer": "CONGO DR",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "COK is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "COOK ISLANDS",
        " second_option": "CONGO DR",
        " third_option": "CHINESE TAIPEI",
        " answer": "COOK ISLANDS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "CRC is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "COSTA RICA",
        " second_option": "COOK ISLANDS",
        " third_option": "CHINESE TAIPEI",
        " answer": "COSTA RICA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "CIV is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "IVORY COAST",
        " second_option": "COOK ISLANDS",
        " third_option": "CROATIA",
        " answer": "IVORY COAST",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "CRO is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "CROATIA",
        " second_option": "COOK ISLANDS",
        " third_option": "CHINA",
        " answer": "CROATIA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "CUB is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "CUBA",
        " second_option": "CONGO DR",
        " third_option": "CHINA",
        " answer": "CUBA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "CUW is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "CURACAO",
        " second_option": "CUBA",
        " third_option": "CHINA",
        " answer": "CURACAO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "CYP is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "CYPRUS",
        " second_option": "CYRUS",
        " third_option": "CHINA",
        " answer": "CYPRUS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "CZE is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "CZECH REPUBLIC",
        " second_option": "CYPRUS",
        " third_option": "CHINA",
        " answer": "CZECH REPUBLIC",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "DEN is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "DENMARK",
        " second_option": "DJIBOUTI",
        " third_option": "DOMINICAN REPUBLIC",
        " answer": "DENMARK",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "DJI is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "DJIBOUTI",
        " second_option": "DENMARK",
        " third_option": "DOMINICAN REPUBLIC",
        " answer": "DJIBOUTI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "DMA is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "DOMINICA",
        " second_option": "DJIBOUTI",
        " third_option": "DOMINICAN REPUBLIC",
        " answer": "DOMINICA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "DOM is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "DOMINICAN REPUBLIC",
        " second_option": "DOMINICA",
        " third_option": "DJIBOUTI",
        " answer": "DOMINICAN REPUBLIC",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "ECU is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "ECUADOR",
        " second_option": "EGYPT",
        " third_option": "EQUITORIAL GUINEA",
        " answer": "ECUADOR",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "EGY is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "EGYPT",
        " second_option": "ECUADOR",
        " third_option": "EQUITORIAL GUINEA",
        " answer": "EGYPT",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "SLV is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "EL SALVADOR",
        " second_option": "EGYPT",
        " third_option": "EQUITORIAL GUINEA",
        " answer": "EL SALVADOR",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "ENG is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "ENGLAND",
        " second_option": "EL SALVADOR",
        " third_option": "EQUITORIAL GUINEA",
        " answer": "ENGLAND",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "EQG is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "ENGLAND",
        " second_option": "EQUITORIAL GUINEA",
        " third_option": "EL SALVADOR",
        " answer": "EQUITORIAL GUINEA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "ERI is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "ENGLAND",
        " second_option": "ERITREA",
        " third_option": "EQUITORIAL GUINEA",
        " answer": "ERITREA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "EST is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "ERITREA",
        " second_option": "ESTONIA",
        " third_option": "EQUITORIAL GUINEA",
        " answer": "ESTONIA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "ETH is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "ESTONIA",
        " second_option": "ETHOPIA",
        " third_option": "EQUITORIAL GUINEA",
        " answer": "ETHOPIA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "FRO is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "FIJI",
        " second_option": "FAROE ISLANDS",
        " third_option": "FINLAND ",
        " answer": "FAROE ISLANDS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "FIJ is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "FAROE ISLANDS",
        " second_option": "FIJI",
        " third_option": "FINLAND ",
        " answer": "FIJI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "FIN is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "FAROE ISLANDS",
        " second_option": "FINLAND ",
        " third_option": "FIJI",
        " answer": "FINLAND ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "FRA is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "FIJI",
        " second_option": "FRANCE",
        " third_option": "FINLAND ",
        " answer": "FRANCE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "GAB is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "GEORGIA",
        " second_option": "GABON",
        " third_option": "GAMBIA",
        " answer": "GABON",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "GAM is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "GEORGIA",
        " second_option": "GAMBIA",
        " third_option": "GABON",
        " answer": "GAMBIA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "GEO is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "GABON",
        " second_option": "GEORGIA",
        " third_option": "GAMBIA",
        " answer": "GEORGIA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "GER is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "GREECE",
        " second_option": "GERMANY",
        " third_option": "GAMBIA",
        " answer": "GERMANY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "GHA is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "GREECE",
        " second_option": "GHANA",
        " third_option": "GIBRALTAR",
        " answer": "GHANA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "GIB is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "GREECE",
        " second_option": "GIBRALTAR",
        " third_option": "GHANA",
        " answer": "GIBRALTAR",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "GRE is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "GRENADA",
        " second_option": "GREECE",
        " third_option": "GHANA",
        " answer": "GREECE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "GRN is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "GUINEA",
        " second_option": "GRENADA",
        " third_option": "GHANA",
        " answer": "GRENADA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "GUM is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "GUINEA",
        " second_option": "GUAM",
        " third_option": "GUATEMALA",
        " answer": "GUAM",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "GUA is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "GUINEA",
        " second_option": "GUATEMALA",
        " third_option": "GUAM",
        " answer": "GUATEMALA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "GUI is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "GUINEA-BISSAU",
        " second_option": "GUINEA",
        " third_option": "GUAM",
        " answer": "GUINEA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "GNB is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "GUYANA",
        " second_option": "GUINEA-BISSAU",
        " third_option": "GUAM",
        " answer": "GUINEA-BISSAU",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "GUY is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "GUINEA-BISSAU",
        " second_option": "GUYANA",
        " third_option": "GUAM",
        " answer": "GUYANA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "HAI is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "HONDURAS",
        " second_option": "HAITI",
        " third_option": "HUNGARY",
        " answer": "HAITI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "HON is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "HUNGARY",
        " second_option": "HONDURAS",
        " third_option": "HAITI",
        " answer": "HONDURAS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "HKG is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "HUNGARY",
        " second_option": "HONG KONG",
        " third_option": "HONDURAS",
        " answer": "HONG KONG",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "HUN is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "HONG KONG",
        " second_option": "HUNGARY",
        " third_option": "HONDURAS",
        " answer": "HUNGARY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "ISL is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "INDIA",
        " second_option": "ICELAND",
        " third_option": "INDONESIA",
        " answer": "ICELAND",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "IND is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "INDIA",
        " second_option": "INDONESIA",
        " third_option": "INDONESIA",
        " answer": "INDIA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "IDN is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "INDONESIA",
        " second_option": "INDIA",
        " third_option": "IRAQ",
        " answer": "INDONESIA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "IRN is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "IRAN",
        " second_option": "INDONESIA",
        " third_option": "IRAQ",
        " answer": "IRAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "IRQ is the FIFA code for which country?",
        " first_option": "IRAQ",
        " second_option": "IRAN",
        " third_option": "INDONESIA",
        " answer": "IRAQ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which footballer has autobiography titled \u201cA goal in the sky\u201d?",
        " first_option": "Zino Doff",
        " second_option": "Eric Cantona",
        " third_option": "Roberto Baggio",
        " answer": "Roberto Baggio",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In 2010 World cup who was the captain of Spain?",
        " first_option": "Edwin Van der Sar",
        " second_option": "Thibaut Courtouis",
        " third_option": "Iker Casillas",
        " answer": "Iker Casillas",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In 2001 who was the \u201cEuropean footballer of the year\u201d?",
        " first_option": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        " second_option": "Eusebio",
        " third_option": "Michael Owen",
        " answer": "Michael Owen",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Diego Maradona played how many World cups?",
        " first_option": "5",
        " second_option": "3",
        " third_option": "4",
        " answer": "4",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Eng is the FIFA code of which country?",
        " first_option": "GHANA",
        " second_option": "Gibraltar",
        " third_option": "England",
        " answer": "England",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The citizens are the nickname of which football club?",
        " first_option": "Manchester United",
        " second_option": "Chelsea",
        " third_option": "Manchester City",
        " answer": "Manchester City",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The national challenge cup is also known as what?",
        " first_option": "Roland Garros ",
        " second_option": "ATP",
        " third_option": "US open cup",
        " answer": "US open cup",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "what vehicle company sponsored 2015 MLS golden boot award?",
        " first_option": "Chevrolet",
        " second_option": "Nissan",
        " third_option": "Audi",
        " answer": "Audi",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "World cup 1958 was held in which country?",
        " first_option": "Switzerland",
        " second_option": "England",
        " third_option": "Sweden",
        " answer": "Sweden",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "From where Maradona makes his professional soccer debut?",
        " first_option": "River Plate ",
        " second_option": "Boca Juniors",
        " third_option": "Argentinos Junior",
        " answer": "Argentinos Junior",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the earlier form of soccer?",
        " first_option": "Tiki Taka",
        " second_option": "Baller ",
        " third_option": "Socca",
        " answer": "Socca",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "According to FIFA which was the earlier form of football?",
        " first_option": "Vuju",
        " second_option": "Buju",
        " third_option": "Cuju",
        " answer": "Cuju",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Centennial America cup 2016 started on which date?",
        " first_option": "3 to 26 August 2016",
        " second_option": "3 to 26 July 2016",
        " third_option": "3 to 26 June 2016",
        " answer": "3 to 26 June 2016",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many teams participated in Copa America Centenario USA 2016 tournament?",
        " first_option": "20",
        " second_option": "12",
        " third_option": "16",
        " answer": "16",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which team won the Centennial cup in 2016?",
        " first_option": "Uruguay",
        " second_option": "Argentina",
        " third_option": "Chile",
        " answer": "Chile",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the runner up team in Copa America cup 2016?",
        " first_option": "Uruguay",
        " second_option": "Chile",
        " third_option": "Argentina",
        " answer": "Argentina",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The number of total matches in Centennial 2016?",
        " first_option": "28",
        " second_option": "24",
        " third_option": "32",
        " answer": "32",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total number of goals in Copa Centenario tournament 2016?",
        " first_option": "110",
        " second_option": "100",
        " third_option": "91",
        " answer": "91",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country hosted the 2016 OFC Nations cup?",
        " first_option": "Ghana",
        " second_option": "Nigeria",
        " third_option": "Papua New Guinea",
        " answer": "Papua New Guinea",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "OFC (Oceania football confederation) headquarter located on which country?",
        " first_option": "Denver, US",
        " second_option": "Faroe Islands",
        " third_option": "Auckland New Zealand",
        " answer": "Auckland New Zealand",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the champion of 2016 OFC Nations cup tournament?",
        " first_option": "Australia",
        " second_option": "DENMARK",
        " third_option": "New Zealand",
        " answer": "New Zealand",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In OFC 2016 Nations Cup tournament which player was the top goal scorer?",
        " first_option": "Didier Drogba",
        " second_option": "Bakary Sahko",
        " third_option": "Raymond Gunemba",
        " answer": "Raymond Gunemba",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In OFC 2016 Nations Cup tournament how many goals was scored by the top goal scorer?",
        " first_option": "6",
        " second_option": "4",
        " third_option": "5",
        " answer": "5",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won the best play award of OFC 2016 tournament?\n",
        " first_option": "Raymond Gunemba",
        " second_option": "Bakary Sahko",
        " third_option": "David Muta",
        " answer": "David Muta",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The best goalkeeper of 2016 OFC tournament was?",
        " first_option": "David Muta",
        " second_option": "Bakary Sahko",
        " third_option": "Stefan Marinovic",
        " answer": "Stefan Marinovic",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What edition was the Euro 2016 organized by UEFA?",
        " first_option": "19th",
        " second_option": "17th",
        " third_option": "15th",
        " answer": "15th",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country hosted Euro 2016 ?",
        " first_option": "Italy",
        " second_option": "Spain",
        " third_option": "France",
        " answer": "France",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What months was the Euro 2016 played ?",
        " first_option": "September/October",
        " second_option": "January/February",
        " third_option": "June/July",
        " answer": "June/July",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many teams participate in Euro 2016?",
        " first_option": "32",
        " second_option": "28",
        " third_option": "24",
        " answer": "24",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which team won 2016 UEFA European championship title?",
        " first_option": "Spain",
        " second_option": "France",
        " third_option": "Portugal",
        " answer": "Portugal",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "2017 confederations cup held in which country?",
        " first_option": "France",
        " second_option": "Portugal",
        " third_option": "Russia",
        " answer": "Russia",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the start and end date of FIFA confederation cup 2017?",
        " first_option": "September/October",
        " second_option": "January/February",
        " third_option": "June/July",
        " answer": "June/July",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many teams participated in 2017 FIFA confederation tournament?",
        " first_option": "10",
        " second_option": "9",
        " third_option": "8",
        " answer": "8",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which team was the champion of the confederation cup 2017?",
        " first_option": "Portugal",
        " second_option": "Russia",
        " third_option": "Germany",
        " answer": "Germany",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The runner-up team of the Confederation 2017 tournament was?",
        " first_option": "Germany",
        " second_option": "Russia",
        " third_option": "Chile",
        " answer": "Chile",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The total number of matches played in confederation cup 2017 was?",
        " first_option": "24",
        " second_option": "20",
        " third_option": "16",
        " answer": "16",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these Players was not a top scorer at the Confederation cup 2017 ?",
        " first_option": "Timo Werner",
        " second_option": "Lars Stindl",
        " third_option": "Thomas Muller",
        " answer": "Thomas Muller",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Fair play award won by which team?",
        " first_option": "Portugal",
        " second_option": "Spain",
        " third_option": "Germany",
        " answer": "Germany",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which team won the 2017 CAF championship?",
        " first_option": "Ivory Coast ",
        " second_option": "Nigeria",
        " third_option": "Cameroon",
        " answer": "Cameroon",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which player won the man of the match 2017 CAF championship finals?",
        " first_option": "Riyadh Mahrez",
        " second_option": "Victor Moses",
        " third_option": "Benjamin Moukandjo",
        " answer": "Benjamin Moukandjo",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country emerged as a champion of FIFA World cup 2018?",
        " first_option": "Spain",
        " second_option": "Germany",
        " third_option": "France",
        " answer": "France",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The final match of the FIFA 2018 World CUP played between which teams? ",
        " first_option": "Germany & Russia",
        " second_option": "France & Germany",
        " third_option": "France & Croatia",
        " answer": "France & Croatia",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The final match of the FIFA 2018 World CUP was played in which stadium? ",
        " first_option": "Stade Louis II",
        " second_option": "Stadio Olimpico",
        " third_option": "Luzhniki Stadium Russia",
        " answer": "Luzhniki Stadium Russia",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the prize money for the winning team of the FIFA 2018 World CUP?",
        " first_option": "37 million US dollar",
        " second_option": "36 million US dollar",
        " third_option": "38 million US dollar",
        " answer": "38 million US dollar",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won the golden ball award 2018 as the best player in World cup 2018?",
        " first_option": "Toni Kroos",
        " second_option": "Cristiano Ronaldo ",
        " third_option": "Luka Modric",
        " answer": "Luka Modric",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country hosted the FIFA World cup 2018?",
        " first_option": "Netherlands",
        " second_option": "Spain",
        " third_option": "Russia",
        " answer": "Russia",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In 2018 World cup final which player got man of the match award?",
        " first_option": "Paul Pogba",
        " second_option": "Kylian Mbappe",
        " third_option": "Antoine Griezmann",
        " answer": "Antoine Griezmann",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Best goalkeeper golden glove award 2018 won by which player?",
        " first_option": "Sam Handanovic",
        " second_option": "Alisson Becker",
        " third_option": "Thibaut Courtois",
        " answer": "Thibaut Courtois",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which England player won the golden boot award in FIFA 2018?",
        " first_option": "Jamie Vardy",
        " second_option": "Wayne Rooney",
        " third_option": "Harry Kane",
        " answer": "Harry Kane",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which team play a fair and disciplined game and won fair play award 2018?",
        " first_option": "Italy",
        " second_option": "England",
        " third_option": "Spain",
        " answer": "Spain",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In which FIFA World cup tournament was the VAR (Video Assistant Referee) first used ?",
        " first_option": "2019",
        " second_option": "2017",
        " third_option": "2018",
        " answer": "2018",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country will host the 2022 FIFA World cup?",
        " first_option": "U.A.E",
        " second_option": "Dubai",
        " third_option": "Qatar",
        " answer": "Qatar",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many time did France win the FIFA World cup?",
        " first_option": "4",
        " second_option": "3",
        " third_option": "2",
        " answer": "2",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you remember the top 4 teams of FIFA World cup 2018?",
        " first_option": "1) Spain 2) Croatia 3) Belgium 4) Russia",
        " second_option": "1) France 2) Croatia 3) Belgium 4) Russia",
        " third_option": "1) France 2) Croatia 3) Belgium 4) England",
        " answer": "1) France 2) Croatia 3) Belgium 4) England",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the youngest player of World cup 2018?",
        " first_option": "Trent Alexander Arnold",
        " second_option": "Erling Haaland",
        " third_option": "Kylian Mbappe",
        " answer": "Kylian Mbappe",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many cities of Russia hosted WC 2018 matches?",
        " first_option": "12",
        " second_option": "9",
        " third_option": "11",
        " answer": "11",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "FIFA 2018 WC was the what edition?",
        " first_option": "20th",
        " second_option": "18th",
        " third_option": "19th",
        " answer": "19th",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of theses teams did not aappear in the FIFA World CUP OF 2018 for the first time?",
        " first_option": "Panama",
        " second_option": "Iceland",
        " third_option": "Japan",
        " answer": "Japan",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which 2 teams were the first time appeared in FIFA 2018?",
        " first_option": "Panama & Japan",
        " second_option": "Japan & South Korea",
        " third_option": "Iceland and Panama",
        " answer": "Iceland and Panama",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The opening match of WC 2018 played between which 2 teams?",
        " first_option": "Russia vs Portugal",
        " second_option": "Russia vs Spain",
        " third_option": "Russia VS Saudi Arabia",
        " answer": "Russia VS Saudi Arabia",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which was the only channel who broadcast FIFA 2018 WC in the USA?",
        " first_option": "Supersport",
        " second_option": "ESPN",
        " third_option": "Fox Sports",
        " answer": "Fox Sports",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "SFA stands for ?",
        " first_option": "Swaziland Football Association",
        " second_option": "Spain Football Association",
        " third_option": "Scottish Football Association",
        " answer": "Scottish Football Association",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Scottish football association is considered to be the _______ oldest football association in the World?",
        " first_option": "3rd",
        " second_option": "1st",
        " third_option": "2nd",
        " answer": "2nd",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many teams are enrolled in Scottish professional football league?",
        " first_option": "46",
        " second_option": "38",
        " third_option": "42",
        " answer": "42",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In how many tiers the Scottish professional football league divided?",
        " first_option": "3 Tiers",
        " second_option": "2 Tiers",
        " third_option": "4 Tiers",
        " answer": "4 Tiers",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "FIFA World cup 2014 champion was?",
        " first_option": "SPAIN",
        " second_option": "BRAZIL",
        " third_option": "GERMANY",
        " answer": "GERMANY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country hosted the 2014 World cup?",
        " first_option": "Spain",
        " second_option": "Germany",
        " third_option": "Brazil",
        " answer": "Brazil",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the only scorer of Scotland on the first match of 2017, which was against Canada?",
        " first_option": "Stefan Marinovic",
        " second_option": "Steve Gunnar",
        " third_option": "Steven Naismith",
        " answer": "Steven Naismith",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In 2017 Scottish Cup final which player initiate the scoring?",
        " first_option": "Stefan Marinovic",
        " second_option": "Steven Naismith",
        " third_option": "Jonny Hayes",
        " answer": "Jonny Hayes",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In 2017 which Scottish premiership manager resigned from his post?",
        " first_option": "Stefan Marinovic",
        " second_option": "Jonny Hayes",
        " third_option": "Mark Warburton",
        " answer": "Mark Warburton",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Scottish player was the top scorer of 2016/17 season?",
        " first_option": "Johnny Hayes",
        " second_option": "Mark Warburton",
        " third_option": "Stuart Armstrong",
        " answer": "Stuart Armstrong",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the only team that participated in each FIFA World CUP so far?",
        " first_option": "SPAIN",
        " second_option": "GERMANY",
        " third_option": "BRAZIL",
        " answer": "BRAZIL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Till now how many teams in total appeared in FIFA World Cup?",
        " first_option": "84",
        " second_option": "80",
        " third_option": "76",
        " answer": "76",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In total how many teams played World Cup final?",
        " first_option": "14",
        " second_option": "10",
        " third_option": "12",
        " answer": "12",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brazuca is the name of what?",
        " first_option": "Football name used in 2010 FIFA World cup",
        " second_option": "Football name used in 2018 FIFA World cup",
        " third_option": "Football name used in 2014 FIFA World cup",
        " answer": "Football name used in 2014 FIFA World cup",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which team won most World cup matches?",
        " first_option": "GERMANY",
        " second_option": "SPAIN",
        " third_option": "BRAZIL",
        " answer": "BRAZIL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the only country who won FIFA WC from 4 different continents?",
        " first_option": "GERMANY",
        " second_option": "SPAIN",
        " third_option": "BRAZIL",
        " answer": "BRAZIL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Los Colchoneros is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Bayer Leverkusen",
        " second_option": "Barcelona",
        " third_option": "Athletico Madrid",
        " answer": "Athletico Madrid",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Blaugrana  is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Bayern Munich",
        " second_option": "Athletico Madrid",
        " third_option": "Barcelona",
        " answer": "Barcelona",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Bavarians is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Barcelona",
        " second_option": "Athletico Madrid",
        " third_option": "Bayern Munich",
        " answer": "Bayern Munich",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Los Blaugranas is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Bayern Munich",
        " second_option": "Barcelona",
        " third_option": "Athletico Madrid",
        " answer": "Athletico Madrid",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Black and Yellows is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Bayern Munich",
        " second_option": "Juventus",
        " third_option": "Borussia Dortmund",
        " answer": "Borussia Dortmund",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Old Lady is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Bayern Munich",
        " second_option": "Leicester City",
        " third_option": "Juventus",
        " answer": "Juventus",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Foxes is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Bayern Munich",
        " second_option": "Juventus",
        " third_option": "Leicester City",
        " answer": "Leicester City",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Works Team is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Leicester City",
        " second_option": "Juventus",
        " third_option": "Bayer Leverkusen",
        " answer": "Bayer Leverkusen",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Citizens is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Bayer Leverkusen",
        " second_option": "Juventus",
        " third_option": "Manchester City",
        " answer": "Manchester City",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Les Rouges et Blancs is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Bayern Munich",
        " second_option": "Juventus",
        " third_option": "Monaco",
        " answer": "Monaco",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Partenopei is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Bayern Munich",
        " second_option": "Monaco",
        " third_option": "Napoli",
        " answer": "Napoli",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "PSG is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Monaco",
        " second_option": "Napoli",
        " third_option": "Paris Saint-Germain",
        " answer": "Paris Saint-Germain",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Drag\u00f5es is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Paris Saint-Germain",
        " second_option": "Napoli",
        " third_option": "Porto",
        " answer": "Porto",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Los Merengues is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Paris Saint-Germain",
        " second_option": "Porto",
        " third_option": "Real Madrid",
        " answer": "Real Madrid",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Yellow Submarine is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Paris Saint-Germain",
        " second_option": "Real Madrid",
        " third_option": "Villareal",
        " answer": "Villareal",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Red Devils is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Villareal",
        " second_option": "Real Madrid",
        " third_option": "Manchester United",
        " answer": "Manchester United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Spurs is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Manchester United",
        " second_option": "Villareal",
        " third_option": "Tottenham Hotspur",
        " answer": "Tottenham Hotspur",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Die Knappen is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Manchester United",
        " second_option": "Tottenham Hotspur",
        " third_option": "Schalke 04",
        " answer": "Schalke 04",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Wolf is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Schalke 05",
        " second_option": "Tottenham Hotspur",
        " third_option": "AS ROMA",
        " answer": "AS ROMA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Les Gones is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "AS ROMA",
        " second_option": "Schalke 06",
        " third_option": "Olympique Lynonnais",
        " answer": "Olympique Lynonnais",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Sons of God is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Schalke 07",
        " second_option": "Olympique Lynonnais",
        " third_option": "Ajax",
        " answer": "Ajax",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Millionaires is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Ajax",
        " second_option": "Olympique Lynonnais",
        " third_option": "River Plate",
        " answer": "River Plate",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Bosteros is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Ajax",
        " second_option": "River Plate",
        " third_option": "Boca Juniors",
        " answer": "Boca Juniors",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Reds is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Ajax",
        " second_option": "AFC Bournemouth",
        " third_option": "Liverpool",
        " answer": "Liverpool",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Cherries is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Ajax",
        " second_option": "Liverpool",
        " third_option": "AFC Bournemouth",
        " answer": "AFC Bournemouth",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Villans is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Leicester City",
        " second_option": "Crystal Palace",
        " third_option": "Aston Villa",
        " answer": "Aston Villa",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Seagulls is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Burnley FC",
        " second_option": "Crystal Palace",
        " third_option": "Brighton & Hove Albions",
        " answer": "Brighton & Hove Albions",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Clarets is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Chelsea",
        " second_option": "Crystal Palace",
        " third_option": "Burnley FC",
        " answer": "Burnley FC",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Blues is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Everton",
        " second_option": "Crystal Palace",
        " third_option": "Chelsea",
        " answer": "Chelsea",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Eagles is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Everton",
        " second_option": "Manchester City",
        " third_option": "Crystal Palace",
        " answer": "Crystal Palace",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Toffees is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Manchester City",
        " second_option": "Newcastle United",
        " third_option": "Everton",
        " answer": "Everton",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Citizens is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Newcastle United",
        " second_option": "Manchester City",
        " third_option": "Norwich City",
        " answer": "Manchester City",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Magpies is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Sheffield United",
        " second_option": "Newcastle United",
        " third_option": "Norwich City",
        " answer": "Newcastle United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Canaries is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Sheffield United",
        " second_option": "Norwich City",
        " third_option": "Newcastle United",
        " answer": "Norwich City",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Blades is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Newcastle United",
        " second_option": "Sheffield United",
        " third_option": "WestHam United",
        " answer": "Sheffield United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Saints is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Watford",
        " second_option": "Southampton",
        " third_option": "WestHam United",
        " answer": "Southampton",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Hornets is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Southampton",
        " second_option": "Watford",
        " third_option": "WestHam United",
        " answer": "Watford",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Hammers is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Southampton",
        " second_option": "WestHam United",
        " third_option": "Wolverhampton Wanderers",
        " answer": "WestHam United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Wanderers is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Southampton",
        " second_option": "Wolverhampton Wanderers",
        " third_option": "Fulham",
        " answer": "Wolverhampton Wanderers",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Cottagers is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Southampton",
        " second_option": "Fulham",
        " third_option": "Wolverhampton Wanderers",
        " answer": "Fulham",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Rams is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Wolverhampton Wanderers",
        " second_option": "Derby County",
        " third_option": "Fulham",
        " answer": "Derby County",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "QPR is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Stoke City",
        " second_option": "Queens Park Rangers",
        " third_option": "Wolverhampton Wanderers",
        " answer": "Queens Park Rangers",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Potters is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Wolverhampton Wanderers",
        " second_option": "Stoke City",
        " third_option": "West Bromich Albion",
        " answer": "Stoke City",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Baggies is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Notthingham Forest",
        " second_option": "West Bromich Albion",
        " third_option": "Wolverhampton Wanderers",
        " answer": "West Bromich Albion",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Swans is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Notthingham Forest",
        " second_option": "Swansea",
        " third_option": "Reading",
        " answer": "Swansea",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Royals is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Notthingham Forest",
        " second_option": "Reading",
        " third_option": "Swansea",
        " answer": "Reading",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Forest is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Swansea",
        " second_option": "Notthingham Forest",
        " third_option": "Hull City",
        " answer": "Notthingham Forest",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Boro is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Notthingham Forest",
        " second_option": "Middlesbrough",
        " third_option": "Hull City",
        " answer": "Middlesbrough",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Tigers is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Notthingham Forest",
        " second_option": "Hull City",
        " third_option": "Middlesbrough",
        " answer": "Hull City",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Rovers is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Middlesbrough",
        " second_option": "Black Burn Rovers",
        " third_option": "Bolton Wanderers",
        " answer": "Black Burn Rovers",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Trotters is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Black Burn Rovers",
        " second_option": "Bolton Wanderers",
        " third_option": "Middlesbrough",
        " answer": "Bolton Wanderers",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Wombles is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Black Burn Rovers",
        " second_option": "AFC Wimbledon",
        " third_option": "Celtic",
        " answer": "AFC Wimbledon",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Celts is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Black Burn Rovers",
        " second_option": "Celtic",
        " third_option": "Gillingham",
        " answer": "Celtic",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Gills is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Black Burn Rovers",
        " second_option": "Gillingham",
        " third_option": "MK Dons",
        " answer": "Gillingham",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Dons is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Black Burn Rovers",
        " second_option": "MK Dons",
        " third_option": "Portsmouth",
        " answer": "MK Dons",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Pompey is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Black Burn Rovers",
        " second_option": "Portsmouth",
        " third_option": "Shrewsbury Town",
        " answer": "Portsmouth",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Shrews is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Black Burn Rovers",
        " second_option": "Shrewsbury Town",
        " third_option": "Portsmouth",
        " answer": "Shrewsbury Town",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Black Cats is a nickname of which team?",
        " first_option": "Portsmouth",
        " second_option": "Sunderland",
        " third_option": "Shrewsbury Town",
        " answer": "Sunderland",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Frank Lampard scored how many goals for Chelsea?",
        " first_option": "199",
        " second_option": "209",
        " third_option": "219",
        " answer": "209",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The 1990 World cup hosted by Italy. Which team was the champion of that tournament?\n",
        " first_option": "Italy",
        " second_option": "Germany",
        " third_option": "Spain",
        " answer": "Germany",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which player won Chelsea player of the year for both 2012 and 2013 ?",
        " first_option": "John Terry",
        " second_option": "Juan Mata",
        " third_option": "Didier Drogba",
        " answer": "Juan Mata",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which player scored the very first goal in the FIFA World cup?",
        " first_option": "Abedi Pele",
        " second_option": "Lucien Laurent",
        " third_option": "Zino Doff",
        " answer": "Lucien Laurent",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the official song of FIFA 2010 World cup?",
        " first_option": "Samina Samina",
        " second_option": "Waka Waka",
        " third_option": "hey hey",
        " answer": "Waka Waka",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many people watched the 2010 FIFA World cup final?",
        " first_option": "2.8 billion",
        " second_option": "3.2 billion",
        " third_option": "3.6 billion",
        " answer": "3.2 billion",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Excluding Antarctica which is the only continent who haven\u2019t yet hosted FIFA World cup?",
        " first_option": "Austria",
        " second_option": "Australia",
        " third_option": "Alaska",
        " answer": "Australia",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The total matches played in 1930 World cup?",
        " first_option": "20",
        " second_option": "18",
        " third_option": "22",
        " answer": "18",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " In FIFA World cup 2018 Germany was fall in which group?",
        " first_option": "Group D",
        " second_option": "Group F",
        " third_option": "Group E",
        " answer": "Group F",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The famous English Soccer player David Backham played senior club football for how many different teams?",
        " first_option": "5",
        " second_option": "6",
        " third_option": "7",
        " answer": "6",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Franco Escobar is part of which clubs 2018 roster?",
        " first_option": "Chelsea",
        " second_option": "Atlanta United",
        " third_option": "Manchester City",
        " answer": "Atlanta United",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is known as the \"King of Soccer\"?",
        " first_option": "Maradona",
        " second_option": "Pele",
        " third_option": "Eusebio",
        " answer": "Pele",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the nickname of the French national soccer team?",
        " first_option": "Les Blancos",
        " second_option": "Les Blues",
        " third_option": "Les Blencs",
        " answer": "Les Blues",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many teams competed in the 2018 FIFA World Cup?",
        " first_option": "28",
        " second_option": "32",
        " third_option": "36",
        " answer": "32",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which confederation is the Turkish national soccer team in?",
        " first_option": "AFA",
        " second_option": "UEFA",
        " third_option": "CEFA",
        " answer": "UEFA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who were Liverpool\u2019s first opponents in the Football League?",
        " first_option": "Everton",
        " second_option": "Middlesbrought Ironopolis",
        " third_option": "Porto",
        " answer": "Middlesbrought Ironopolis",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was the 1980 European Cup Winners\u2019 Cup Final held?",
        " first_option": "England",
        " second_option": "Belgium",
        " third_option": "France",
        " answer": "Belgium",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was the 2006 Champions League Final held?",
        " first_option": "Rome",
        " second_option": "Paris",
        " third_option": "London",
        " answer": "Paris",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the World\u2019s largest football ground?",
        " first_option": "Luzhniki Stadium",
        " second_option": "Rungrado 1st of May Stadium",
        " third_option": "Camp Nou",
        " answer": "Rungrado 1st of May Stadium",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the highest number of goals that FC Barcelona has scored in a league season?",
        " first_option": "130",
        " second_option": "116",
        " third_option": "156",
        " answer": "116",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was the final venue of the oldest footbal clubs championship ?",
        " first_option": "Wembley Stadium",
        " second_option": "The Oval, London",
        " third_option": "London Stadium",
        " answer": "The Oval, London",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liverpool\u2019s win of the European Cup in 1976 -77 was only the second by a British club. Who were the first?",
        " first_option": "Chelsea",
        " second_option": "Glasgow Celtic",
        " third_option": "Manchester United",
        " answer": "Glasgow Celtic",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " When was the first World cup championship held?",
        " first_option": "1940",
        " second_option": "1930",
        " third_option": "1950",
        " answer": "1930",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Where was the first World cup championship held?",
        " first_option": "Germany",
        " second_option": "Uruguay",
        " third_option": "Spain",
        " answer": "Uruguay",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won the Premier League 2012-13?",
        " first_option": "Chelsea",
        " second_option": "Manchester United",
        " third_option": "Manchester City",
        " answer": "Manchester United",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who were the first host nation to go out in the first round of the World cup?",
        " first_option": "Nigeria",
        " second_option": "South Africa ",
        " third_option": "Ivory Coast ",
        " answer": "South Africa ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many nations in africa have hosted the World cup ?",
        " first_option": "2",
        " second_option": "1",
        " third_option": "3",
        " answer": "1",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who were the first host nation to go out in the first round of the World cup?",
        " first_option": "Dennis Law",
        " second_option": "Jules Rimet",
        " third_option": "Franz Beckenbauer",
        " answer": "Jules Rimet",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has scored the most hat tricks in La Liga for Barcelona?",
        " first_option": "Raul",
        " second_option": "Lionel Messi",
        " third_option": "Cristiano Ronaldo ",
        " answer": "Lionel Messi",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " What do the two football Dundee United F.C. and Celtic F.C have in common?",
        " first_option": "England",
        " second_option": "Scotland",
        " third_option": "Wales",
        " answer": "Scotland",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who scored Liverpool\u2019s only goal in the 1978 European Cup Final?",
        " first_option": "Steven Naismith",
        " second_option": "Kenny Dlagish",
        " third_option": "Micheal Wender",
        " answer": "Kenny Dlagish",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the player to have been capped most often by his country?",
        " first_option": "Victor Valdez",
        " second_option": "H\u00e9ctor Chumpitaz.",
        " third_option": "Didier Drogba",
        " answer": "H\u00e9ctor Chumpitaz.",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Barcelona players have won the World Player of the Year award?",
        " first_option": "3",
        " second_option": "5",
        " third_option": "4",
        " answer": "5",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Copa Libertadores mean?",
        " first_option": "The South American League",
        " second_option": "The South American Cup for Clubs.",
        " third_option": "The South America Trophy",
        " answer": "The South American Cup for Clubs.",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mark Hateley was top scorer in 1984 and then sold to which club?",
        " first_option": "Roma",
        " second_option": "AC Milan",
        " third_option": "Everton",
        " answer": "AC Milan",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the oldest member of a World Cup Winning Team?",
        " first_option": "Eusebio",
        " second_option": "Dino Zoff",
        " third_option": "Fabio Cannavaro",
        " answer": "Dino Zoff",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first winner of the \u201cGolden Boot Award\u201d ?",
        " first_option": "Dino Zoff",
        " second_option": "Eusebio",
        " third_option": "Franz Beckenbauer",
        " answer": "Eusebio",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did Eusebio win his first Golden Boot Award ?",
        " first_option": "1965/66",
        " second_option": "1967/68",
        " third_option": "1965/67",
        " answer": "1967/68",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "When did a sixteen year old Alan Knight make his League debut?",
        " first_option": "1980",
        " second_option": "1978",
        " third_option": "9182",
        " answer": "1978",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you score a goal directly from a flag kick ?",
        " first_option": "No",
        " second_option": "Yes",
        " third_option": "Impossible",
        " answer": "Yes",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Houston Texans mascot?",
        " first_option": "El Macho",
        " second_option": "Toro",
        " third_option": "Pintos",
        " answer": "Toro",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you be \u2018off side\u2019 from a flag kick?",
        " first_option": "No",
        " second_option": "Yes",
        " third_option": "Impossible",
        " answer": "Yes",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was known as \u2018Mad Dog\u2019?",
        " first_option": "Kenny Dlagish",
        " second_option": "Martin Allen",
        " third_option": "Fabio Cannavaro",
        " answer": "Martin Allen",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many countries took part in first World Cup Championship ?",
        " first_option": "11",
        " second_option": "13",
        " third_option": "15",
        " answer": "13",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cNittany Lion\u201d is the mascot for which college team?",
        " first_option": "Texas State University",
        " second_option": "Penn State University",
        " third_option": "Georgia Tech University",
        " answer": "Penn State University",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country won the Jules Rimet Trophy outright by winning the World cup four times?",
        " first_option": "Argentina",
        " second_option": "Brazil",
        " third_option": "Ecuador",
        " answer": "Brazil",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which former \u2018Footballer of the Year\u2019 went to play for Nagoya Grampus Eight?",
        " first_option": "Waynre Rooney",
        " second_option": "Gary Lineker",
        " third_option": "Phil Bardsley",
        " answer": "Gary Lineker",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which countries have won the World cup thrice?",
        " first_option": "Italy & Brazil",
        " second_option": "Italy & West Germany",
        " third_option": "Italy & France",
        " answer": "Italy & West Germany",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the highest number of goals that Manchester United has scored in a league season?",
        " first_option": "96",
        " second_option": "103",
        " third_option": "108",
        " answer": "103",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has played in the maximum number of World Cup Competitions?",
        " first_option": "Carlos Puyol",
        " second_option": "Antonio Carbajal",
        " third_option": "Oliver Kahn",
        " answer": "Antonio Carbajal",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Czech Republic player scored a hat-trick for Liverpool against Chelsea in 1997?",
        " first_option": "Kenny Dalgish ",
        " second_option": "Patrick Berger",
        " third_option": "Roy Keane",
        " answer": "Patrick Berger",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the only player to have been a member of the World Cup winning team thrice?",
        " first_option": "Maradona",
        " second_option": "Pele",
        " third_option": "Eusebio",
        " answer": "Pele",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Manchester United\u2019s training ground better known as?",
        " first_option": "Goodison Park",
        " second_option": "Carrington",
        " third_option": "Signal Iduna",
        " answer": "Carrington",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who holds the record of most goals scored in a single World Cup Com-petition?",
        " first_option": "Phil Neville",
        " second_option": "Just Fontaine",
        " third_option": "Phil Bardsley",
        " answer": "Just Fontaine",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which London club was the first Premiership team to be relegated twice?",
        " first_option": "Sunderland",
        " second_option": "Crystal Palace",
        " third_option": "Newcastle United ",
        " answer": "Crystal Palace",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is nick-named \u2018Der Kaiser\u2019?",
        " first_option": "Dino Zoff",
        " second_option": "Franz Beckenbauer",
        " third_option": "Eusebio",
        " answer": "Franz Beckenbauer",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has scored the most hat tricks for Manchester United?",
        " first_option": "Wayne Rooney",
        " second_option": "Dennis Law",
        " third_option": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        " answer": "Dennis Law",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Pele's real name ?",
        " first_option": "Edson Arantes",
        " second_option": "Edson Arantes do Nascimento.",
        " third_option": "Arantes do Nascimento.",
        " answer": "Edson Arantes do Nascimento.",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Birmingham City player was responsible for the tackle that broke Eduardo\u2019s leg in 2008?",
        " first_option": "Martin Tyler",
        " second_option": "Martin Taylor",
        " third_option": "Sergei Brin",
        " answer": "Martin Taylor",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the best football player of Europe in 1998?",
        " first_option": "Micheal Owen",
        " second_option": "Zinedine Zidane",
        " third_option": "Franz Beckenbauer",
        " answer": "Zinedine Zidane",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the longer sides of a football pitch called?",
        " first_option": "Longlines",
        " second_option": "Touchlines",
        " third_option": "Sidelines",
        " answer": "Touchlines",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the shorter sides of a football pitch called?",
        " first_option": "Longlines",
        " second_option": "Goal Lines",
        " third_option": "Touchlines",
        " answer": "Goal Lines",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the prize for the best football player of Europe?",
        " first_option": "Silver Football",
        " second_option": "Golden Football",
        " third_option": "MVP",
        " answer": "Golden Football",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Where did legendary goalkeeper David Seaman go after leaving Arsenal?",
        " first_option": "Manchester United",
        " second_option": "Manchester City",
        " third_option": "Tottenham ",
        " answer": "Manchester City",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which American Club did Pele play for in his last playing days?",
        " first_option": "River Plate",
        " second_option": "Cosmos",
        " third_option": "Santos",
        " answer": "Cosmos",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which was the first football club to founded?",
        " first_option": "Portsmouth",
        " second_option": "Sheffield FC",
        " third_option": "Newcastle United ",
        " answer": "Sheffield FC",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Of which Brazilian Club was Pele a member?",
        " first_option": "",
        " second_option": "Santos",
        " third_option": "Cosmos",
        " answer": "Santos",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two Arsenal players were sent off versus Chelsea in September 2015?",
        " first_option": "Gabriel Paulista and Mikel Arteta",
        " second_option": "Gabriel Paulista and Santi Cazorla.",
        " third_option": "Gabriel Paulista and Patrick Vieira",
        " answer": "Gabriel Paulista and Santi Cazorla.",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Pele\u2019s career record before he joined Cosmos?",
        " first_option": "1161 goals",
        " second_option": "1216 goals",
        " third_option": "1316 goals",
        " answer": "1216 goals",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "how many career goals does pele have ?",
        " first_option": "1181 goals",
        " second_option": "1281 goals",
        " third_option": "1381 goals",
        " answer": "1281 goals",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "how many career goals does maradona have ?",
        " first_option": "359 goals",
        " second_option": "259 goals",
        " third_option": "459 goals",
        " answer": "259 goals",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "how many career goals does Lampard have ?",
        " first_option": "191 goals",
        " second_option": "211 goals",
        " third_option": "251 goals",
        " answer": "211 goals",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "how many career goals does Gerrard have ?",
        " first_option": "150 goals",
        " second_option": "120 goals",
        " third_option": "180 goals",
        " answer": "120 goals",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "how many career goals does Lineker have ?",
        " first_option": "300 goals",
        " second_option": "330 goals",
        " third_option": "360 goals",
        " answer": "330 goals",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "how many career goals does Shearer have ?",
        " first_option": "83 goals",
        " second_option": "283 goals",
        " third_option": "183 goals",
        " answer": "283 goals",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "how many career goals does Owen have ?",
        " first_option": "150 goals",
        " second_option": "100 goals",
        " third_option": "200 goals",
        " answer": "150 goals",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "how many career goals does Rooney have ?",
        " first_option": "208 goals",
        " second_option": "148 goals",
        " third_option": "178 goals",
        " answer": "208 goals",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "how many career goals does Denis Law have ?",
        " first_option": "171 goals",
        " second_option": "71 goals",
        " third_option": "271 goals",
        " answer": "171 goals",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "how many career goals does Henry have ?",
        " first_option": "228 goals",
        " second_option": "128 goals",
        " third_option": "328 goals",
        " answer": "228 goals",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "how many career goals does Cantona have ?",
        " first_option": "82 goals",
        " second_option": "182 goals",
        " third_option": "282 goals",
        " answer": "82 goals",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "how many career goals does Drogba have ?",
        " first_option": "159 goals",
        " second_option": "59 goals",
        " third_option": "259 goals",
        " answer": "159 goals",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "how many career goals does Beckham have?",
        " first_option": "127 goals",
        " second_option": "73 goals",
        " third_option": "100 goals",
        " answer": "127 goals",
        " difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BECKHAM\"?",
        " first_option": "David ",
        " second_option": "Rio",
        " third_option": "Steven",
        " answer": "David ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GERARD\"?",
        " first_option": "Steven",
        " second_option": "Rio",
        " third_option": "David ",
        " answer": "Steven",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"FERDINAND\"?",
        " first_option": "Rio",
        " second_option": "David ",
        " third_option": "Steven",
        " answer": "Rio",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"OKOCHA\"?",
        " first_option": "Austin",
        " second_option": "Rio",
        " third_option": "Steven",
        " answer": "Austin",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KANU\"?",
        " first_option": "Nwankwo",
        " second_option": "Austin",
        " third_option": "Steven",
        " answer": "Nwankwo",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SHEARER\"?",
        " first_option": "Alan",
        " second_option": "Nwankwo",
        " third_option": "Steven",
        " answer": "Alan",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"OWEN\"?",
        " first_option": "Micheal",
        " second_option": "Owen",
        " third_option": "Nwankwo",
        " answer": "Micheal",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"HEGREAVES\"?",
        " first_option": "Owen",
        " second_option": "Nwankwo",
        " third_option": "Micheal",
        " answer": "Owen",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MILITO\"?",
        " first_option": "Diego",
        " second_option": "Tim",
        " third_option": "Nwankwo",
        " answer": "Diego",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GABIADINI\"?",
        " first_option": "Manolo",
        " second_option": "Tim",
        " third_option": "Diego",
        " answer": "Manolo",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"HOWARD\"?",
        " first_option": "Tim",
        " second_option": "Manolo",
        " third_option": "Diego",
        " answer": "Tim",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SCHMEICHEL\"?",
        " first_option": "Casper",
        " second_option": "Manolo",
        " third_option": "Tim",
        " answer": "Casper",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KLUIVERT\"?",
        " first_option": "Justin",
        " second_option": "Tim",
        " third_option": "Casper",
        " answer": "Justin",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GATTUSO\"?",
        " first_option": "Gennaro",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Casper",
        " answer": "Gennaro",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"NEDVED\"?",
        " first_option": "Pavel",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Gennaro",
        " answer": "Pavel",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GIGGS\"?",
        " first_option": "Rtyan",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Pavel",
        " answer": "Rtyan",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DUNK\"?",
        " first_option": "Lewis",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Ryan",
        " answer": "Lewis",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SCHOLES\"?",
        " first_option": "Paul",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Lewis",
        " answer": "Paul",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KEANE\"?",
        " first_option": "Roy",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Dwight",
        " answer": "Roy",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"YORKE\"?",
        " first_option": "Dwight",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Roy",
        " answer": "Dwight",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"NEVILLE\"?",
        " first_option": "Phil",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Dwight",
        " answer": "Phil",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"NEVILLEE\"?",
        " first_option": "Gary",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Phil",
        " answer": "Gary",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CANTONA\"?",
        " first_option": "Eric",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Gary",
        " answer": "Eric",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VAN DER SAR\"?",
        " first_option": "Edwin",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Eric",
        " answer": "Edwin",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"EVRA\"?",
        " first_option": "Patrice",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Edwin",
        " answer": "Patrice",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"HEINZE\"?",
        " first_option": "Gabriel",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Patrice",
        " answer": "Gabriel",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"O'SHEA\"?",
        " first_option": "John",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Gabriel",
        " answer": "John",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SILVESTRE\"?",
        " first_option": "Mikael",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "John",
        " answer": "Mikael",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"STAAM\"?",
        " first_option": "Jaap",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Mikael",
        " answer": "Jaap",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VIDIC\"?",
        " first_option": "Nemanja",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Jaap",
        " answer": "Nemanja",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"FLETCHER\"?",
        " first_option": "Darren",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Nemanja",
        " answer": "Darren",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GIBSON\"?",
        " first_option": "Darron",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Darren",
        " answer": "Darron",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"PARK\"?",
        " first_option": "Ji-Sung",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Darron",
        " answer": "Ji-Sung",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"RONALDO\"?",
        " first_option": "Cristiano",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Wayne",
        " answer": "Cristiano",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MESSI\"?",
        " first_option": "Lionel",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Wayne",
        " answer": "Lionel",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ROONEY\"?",
        " first_option": "Wayne",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Lionel",
        " answer": "Wayne",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ROSSI\"?",
        " first_option": "Guiseppe",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Ruud",
        " answer": "Guiseppe",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"Van Nistelrooy\"?",
        " first_option": "Ruud",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Guiseppe",
        " answer": "Ruud",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LAMPARD\"?",
        " first_option": "Frank",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Ruud",
        " answer": "Frank",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DROGBA\"?",
        " first_option": "Didier",
        " second_option": "Justin",
        " third_option": "Frank",
        " answer": "Didier",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KALOU\"?",
        " first_option": "SALOMON",
        " second_option": "Frank",
        " third_option": "Didier",
        " answer": "SALOMON",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BENT\"?",
        " first_option": "DARREN",
        " second_option": "SALOMON",
        " third_option": "Didier",
        " answer": "DARREN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"HENRY\"?",
        " first_option": "THIERRY",
        " second_option": "SALOMON",
        " third_option": "DARREN",
        " answer": "THIERRY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VIEIRA\"?",
        " first_option": "PATRICE",
        " second_option": "DARREN",
        " third_option": "THIERRY",
        " answer": "PATRICE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LJUNGBERG\"?",
        " first_option": "FREDDIE",
        " second_option": "PATRICE",
        " third_option": "THIERRY",
        " answer": "FREDDIE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ARTETA\"?",
        " first_option": "MIKEL",
        " second_option": "ANTONIO",
        " third_option": "THIERRY",
        " answer": "MIKEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CONTE\"?",
        " first_option": "ANTONIO",
        " second_option": "MIKEL",
        " third_option": "THIERRY",
        " answer": "ANTONIO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GALLAS\"?",
        " first_option": "WILLIAM",
        " second_option": "MIKEL",
        " third_option": "ANTONIO",
        " answer": "WILLIAM",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LEHMANN\"?",
        " first_option": "JENS",
        " second_option": "MIKEL",
        " third_option": "WILLIAM",
        " answer": "JENS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ALMUNIA\"?",
        " first_option": "MANUEL",
        " second_option": "JENS",
        " third_option": "WILLIAM",
        " answer": "MANUEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CAMPBELL\"?",
        " first_option": "SOL",
        " second_option": "MANUEL",
        " third_option": "WILLIAM",
        " answer": "SOL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"TOURE\"?",
        " first_option": "KOLO",
        " second_option": "MANUEL",
        " third_option": "SOL",
        " answer": "KOLO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"TOURE\"?",
        " first_option": "YAYA",
        " second_option": "MANUEL",
        " third_option": "PHILLIPE",
        " answer": "YAYA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SENDEROS\"?",
        " first_option": "PHILLIPE",
        " second_option": "MANUEL",
        " third_option": "ASHLEY",
        " answer": "PHILLIPE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"COLE\"?",
        " first_option": "ASHLEY",
        " second_option": "MANUEL",
        " third_option": "GAEL",
        " answer": "ASHLEY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CLICHY\"?",
        " first_option": "GAEL",
        " second_option": "MANUEL",
        " third_option": "ASHLEY",
        " answer": "GAEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"EBOUE\"?",
        " first_option": "EMMANUEL",
        " second_option": "MANUEL",
        " third_option": "GILBERTO",
        " answer": "EMMANUEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GILBERT\"?",
        " first_option": "KERREA",
        " second_option": "EMMANUEL",
        " third_option": "GILBERTO",
        " answer": "KERREA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SILVA\"?",
        " first_option": "GILBERTO",
        " second_option": "KERREA",
        " third_option": "EMMANUEL",
        " answer": "GILBERTO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SILVA\"?",
        " first_option": "DAVID",
        " second_option": "KERREA",
        " third_option": "MICHEL",
        " answer": "DAVID",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BASTOS\"?",
        " first_option": "MICHEL",
        " second_option": "KERREA",
        " third_option": "DAVID",
        " answer": "MICHEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"NAVAS\"?",
        " first_option": "JESUS",
        " second_option": "DAVID",
        " third_option": "MICHEL",
        " answer": "JESUS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"JESUS\"?",
        " first_option": "GABRIEL",
        " second_option": "SEBASTIAN",
        " third_option": "MICHEL",
        " answer": "GABRIEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"FIRMINO\"?",
        " first_option": "BOBBY",
        " second_option": "SEBASTIAN",
        " third_option": "GABRIEL",
        " answer": "BOBBY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SONG\"?",
        " first_option": "ALEX",
        " second_option": "SEBASTIAN",
        " third_option": "BOBBY",
        " answer": "ALEX",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"FABREGAS\"?",
        " first_option": "CESC",
        " second_option": "SEBASTIAN",
        " third_option": "ALEX",
        " answer": "CESC",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LARSSON\"?",
        " first_option": "SEBASTIAN",
        " second_option": "ALEX",
        " third_option": "CESC",
        " answer": "SEBASTIAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DIABY\"?",
        " first_option": "ABOU",
        " second_option": "SEBASTIAN",
        " third_option": "CESC",
        " answer": "ABOU",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"PIRES\"?",
        " first_option": "ROBERT",
        " second_option": "SEBASTIAN",
        " third_option": "ALEKSANDR",
        " answer": "ROBERT",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"HLEB\"?",
        " first_option": "ALEKSANDR",
        " second_option": "SEBASTIAN",
        " third_option": "ROBERT",
        " answer": "ALEKSANDR",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"WALCOTT\"?",
        " first_option": "THEO",
        " second_option": "SEBASTIAN",
        " third_option": "ROBERT",
        " answer": "THEO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ADEBAYOR\"?",
        " first_option": "EMMANUEL",
        " second_option": "THEO",
        " third_option": "DENNIS",
        " answer": "EMMANUEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BENDTNER\"?",
        " first_option": "NIKLAS",
        " second_option": "EMMANUEL",
        " third_option": "DENNIS",
        " answer": "NIKLAS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SZCZESNY\"?",
        " first_option": "WOJCIECH",
        " second_option": "EMMANUEL",
        " third_option": "DAVID",
        " answer": "WOJCIECH",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"OSPINA\"?",
        " first_option": "DAVID",
        " second_option": "EMMANUEL",
        " third_option": "PER",
        " answer": "DAVID",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KOSCIELNY\"?",
        " first_option": "LAURENT",
        " second_option": "DAVID",
        " third_option": "PER",
        " answer": "LAURENT",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MERTESACKER\"?",
        " first_option": "PER",
        " second_option": "LAURENT",
        " third_option": "DAVID",
        " answer": "PER",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GIBBS\"?",
        " first_option": "KIERAN",
        " second_option": "LAURENT",
        " third_option": "PER",
        " answer": "KIERAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DEBUCHY\"?",
        " first_option": "MATHIEU",
        " second_option": "JOHN",
        " third_option": "PER",
        " answer": "MATHIEU",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"OBI MIKEL\"?",
        " first_option": "JOHN",
        " second_option": "MATHIEU",
        " third_option": "PER",
        " answer": "JOHN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DIOUF\"?",
        " first_option": "EL HADJI",
        " second_option": "MATHIEU",
        " third_option": "JOHN",
        " answer": "EL HADJI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KANOUTE\"?",
        " first_option": "FREDERIC",
        " second_option": "JOHN",
        " third_option": "EL HADJI",
        " answer": "FREDERIC",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"EZZAKI\"?",
        " first_option": "BADOU",
        " second_option": "FREDERIC",
        " third_option": "EL HADJI",
        " answer": "BADOU",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GYAN\"?",
        " first_option": "ASAMOAH",
        " second_option": "BADOU",
        " third_option": "EL HADJI",
        " answer": "ASAMOAH",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"YEKINI\"?",
        " first_option": "RASHIDI",
        " second_option": "VIRGIL",
        " third_option": "BADOU",
        " answer": "RASHIDI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KIETA\"?",
        " first_option": "NABY",
        " second_option": "VIRGIL",
        " third_option": "JORDAN",
        " answer": "NABY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"HENDERSON\"?",
        " first_option": "JORDAN",
        " second_option": "VIRGIL",
        " third_option": "SOL",
        " answer": "JORDAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VAN DIJK\"?",
        " first_option": "VIRGIL",
        " second_option": "TRENT",
        " third_option": "JORDAN",
        " answer": "VIRGIL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ALEXANDER ARNOLD\"?",
        " first_option": "TRENT",
        " second_option": "VIRGIL",
        " third_option": "JORDAN",
        " answer": "TRENT",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ROBERSTON\"?",
        " first_option": "ANDREW",
        " second_option": "VIRGIL",
        " third_option": "TRENT",
        " answer": "ANDREW",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MATIP\"?",
        " first_option": "JOEL",
        " second_option": "VIRGIL",
        " third_option": "ANDREW",
        " answer": "JOEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LOVREN\"?",
        " first_option": "DEJAN",
        " second_option": "JOEL",
        " third_option": "ANDREW",
        " answer": "DEJAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"OXLADE CHAMBERLAIN\"?",
        " first_option": "ALEX",
        " second_option": "DEJAN",
        " third_option": "ANDREW",
        " answer": "ALEX",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LALLANA\"?",
        " first_option": "ADAAM",
        " second_option": "DEJAN",
        " third_option": "ALEX",
        " answer": "ADAAM",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SALAH\"?",
        " first_option": "DEJAN",
        " second_option": "MOHAMMED",
        " third_option": "ADAAM",
        " answer": "MOHAMMED",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SHAQIRI\"?",
        " first_option": "DIVOCK",
        " second_option": "XHERDAN",
        " third_option": "ADAAM",
        " answer": "XHERDAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ORIGI\"?",
        " first_option": "MICHY",
        " second_option": "DIVOCK",
        " third_option": "ADAAM",
        " answer": "DIVOCK",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BATSHUAYI\"?",
        " first_option": "DIVOCK",
        " second_option": "MICHY",
        " third_option": "ADAAM",
        " answer": "MICHY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"REINA\"?",
        " first_option": "MICHY",
        " second_option": "PEPE",
        " third_option": "ADAAM",
        " answer": "PEPE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CAVLIERI\"?",
        " first_option": "MICHY",
        " second_option": "DIEGO",
        " third_option": "JAMIE",
        " answer": "DIEGO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CARRAGHER\"?",
        " first_option": "MICHY",
        " second_option": "JAMIE",
        " third_option": "DIEGO",
        " answer": "JAMIE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SKRTEL\"?",
        " first_option": "DANIEL",
        " second_option": "MARTIN",
        " third_option": "DIEGO",
        " answer": "MARTIN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"AGGER\"?",
        " first_option": "GLEN",
        " second_option": "DANIEL",
        " third_option": "DIEGO",
        " answer": "DANIEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"AYALA\"?",
        " first_option": "GLEN",
        " second_option": "DANIEL",
        " third_option": "DANIEL",
        " answer": "DANIEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"JOHNSON\"?",
        " first_option": "DANIEL",
        " second_option": "GLEN",
        " third_option": "DANIEL",
        " answer": "GLEN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MASCHERANO\"?",
        " first_option": "ALBERTO",
        " second_option": "JAVIER",
        " third_option": "DANIEL",
        " answer": "JAVIER",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LEIVA\"?",
        " first_option": "ALBERTO",
        " second_option": "LUCAS",
        " third_option": "MAXI",
        " answer": "LUCAS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"AQUILANI\"?",
        " first_option": "MAXI",
        " second_option": "ALBERTO",
        " third_option": "LUCAS",
        " answer": "ALBERTO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"RODRIGUEZ\"?",
        " first_option": "DIRK",
        " second_option": "MAXI",
        " third_option": "LUCAS",
        " answer": "MAXI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KUYT\"?",
        " first_option": "YOSSI",
        " second_option": "DIRK",
        " third_option": "LUCAS",
        " answer": "DIRK",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BENAYOUN\"?",
        " first_option": "DIRK",
        " second_option": "YOSSI",
        " third_option": "LUCAS",
        " answer": "YOSSI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VORONIN\"?",
        " first_option": "DIRK",
        " second_option": "ANDRII",
        " third_option": "YOSSI",
        " answer": "ANDRII",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"IBRAHIMOVIC\"?",
        " first_option": "DIRK",
        " second_option": "ZLATAN",
        " third_option": "YOSSI",
        " answer": "ZLATAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"TORRES\"?",
        " first_option": "DIRK",
        " second_option": "FERNANDO",
        " third_option": "SIM",
        " answer": "FERNANDO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"N'GOG\"?",
        " first_option": "XABI",
        " second_option": "DAVID",
        " third_option": "SIM",
        " answer": "DAVID",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ALONSO\"?",
        " first_option": "DAVID",
        " second_option": "XABI",
        " third_option": "SIM",
        " answer": "XABI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MIGNOLET\"?",
        " first_option": "DAVID",
        " second_option": "SIM",
        " third_option": "XAVI",
        " answer": "SIM",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SAKO\"?",
        " first_option": "XAVI",
        " second_option": "BAKARY",
        " third_option": "ALY",
        " answer": "BAKARY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SAKHO\"?",
        " first_option": "VICTOR",
        " second_option": "MAMDOU",
        " third_option": "ALY",
        " answer": "MAMDOU",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CISSOKHO\"?",
        " first_option": "VICTOR",
        " second_option": "ALY",
        " third_option": "MASON",
        " answer": "ALY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MOSES\"?",
        " first_option": "MASON",
        " second_option": "VICTOR",
        " third_option": "ALY",
        " answer": "VICTOR",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"STERLING\"?",
        " first_option": "VICTOR",
        " second_option": "RAHEEM",
        " third_option": "ALY",
        " answer": "RAHEEM",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ASPAS\"?",
        " first_option": "LLORIS",
        " second_option": "IAGO",
        " third_option": "ALY",
        " answer": "IAGO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KARIUS\"?",
        " first_option": "ALY",
        " second_option": "PHILIPPE",
        " third_option": "LORIS",
        " answer": "LORIS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"COUTINHO\"?",
        " first_option": "ALBERTO",
        " second_option": "DAVID",
        " third_option": "PHILIPPE",
        " answer": "PHILIPPE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"INGS\"?",
        " first_option": "ALBERTO",
        " second_option": "DANIEL",
        " third_option": "DANNY",
        " answer": "DANNY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"STURRIDGE\"?",
        " first_option": "ALBERTO",
        " second_option": "PETER",
        " third_option": "DANIEL",
        " answer": "DANIEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CECH\"?",
        " first_option": "ALBERTO",
        " second_option": "DANIEL",
        " third_option": "PETR",
        " answer": "PETR",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CUDICINI\"?",
        " first_option": "HENRIQUE",
        " second_option": "DANIEL",
        " third_option": "CARLO",
        " answer": "CARLO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"HILARIO\"?",
        " first_option": "CARLOS",
        " second_option": "DANIEL",
        " third_option": "HENRIQUE",
        " answer": "HENRIQUE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CARVALHO\"?",
        " first_option": "CARLOS",
        " second_option": "JOHN",
        " third_option": "RICARDO",
        " answer": "RICARDO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"TERRY\"?",
        " first_option": "CARLOS",
        " second_option": "RYAN",
        " third_option": "JOHN",
        " answer": "JOHN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BERTRAND\"?",
        " first_option": "CARLOS",
        " second_option": "LASSANA",
        " third_option": "RYAN",
        " answer": "RYAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DIARRA\"?",
        " first_option": "CARLOS",
        " second_option": "RYAN",
        " third_option": "LASSANA",
        " answer": "LASSANA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MAKELELE\"?",
        " first_option": "JORDAN",
        " second_option": "RYAN",
        " third_option": "CLAUDE",
        " answer": "CLAUDE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BALLACK\"?",
        " first_option": "JORDAN",
        " second_option": "JORDAN",
        " third_option": "MICHEAL",
        " answer": "MICHEAL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"COLE\"?",
        " first_option": "JORDAN",
        " second_option": "JAMIE",
        " third_option": "JOE",
        " answer": "JOE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SINCLAIR\"?",
        " first_option": "JORDAN",
        " second_option": "JAMIE",
        " third_option": "SCOTT",
        " answer": "SCOTT",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ROBBEN\"?",
        " first_option": "JORDAN",
        " second_option": "JAMIE",
        " third_option": "ARJEN",
        " answer": "ARJEN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SAHAR\"?",
        " first_option": "JORDAN",
        " second_option": "JAMIE",
        " third_option": "BEN",
        " answer": "BEN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"IVANOVIC\"?",
        " first_option": "JORDAN",
        " second_option": "JAMIE",
        " third_option": "BRANISLAV",
        " answer": "BRANISLAV",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LUIZ\"?",
        " first_option": "JORDAN",
        " second_option": "JAMIE",
        " third_option": "DAVID",
        " answer": "DAVID",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ZHIRKOV\"?",
        " first_option": "JORDAN",
        " second_option": "JAMIE",
        " third_option": "YURI",
        " answer": "YURI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VAN AANHOLT\"?",
        " first_option": "JORDAN",
        " second_option": "JAMIE",
        " third_option": "PATRICK",
        " answer": "PATRICK",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"FERREIRA\"?",
        " first_option": "JORDAN",
        " second_option": "JAMIE",
        " third_option": "PAULO",
        " answer": "PAULO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ESSIEN\"?",
        " first_option": "JORDAN",
        " second_option": "JAMIE",
        " third_option": "MICHEAL",
        " answer": "MICHEAL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MALOUDA\"?",
        " first_option": "JORDAN",
        " second_option": "JAMIE",
        " third_option": "FLORENT",
        " answer": "FLORENT",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ANELKA\"?",
        " first_option": "JAMIE",
        " second_option": "WILLY",
        " third_option": "NIKOLAS",
        " answer": "NIKOLAS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GILMOUR\"?",
        " first_option": "ALBERT",
        " second_option": "WILLY",
        " third_option": "BILLY",
        " answer": "BILLY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KEPA\"?",
        " first_option": "ANTOINE",
        " second_option": "WILLY",
        " third_option": "ARRIZABALAGA",
        " answer": "ARRIZABALAGA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CABALLERO\"?",
        " first_option": "ALBERT",
        " second_option": "ANTOINE",
        " third_option": "WILLY",
        " answer": "WILLY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"RUDIGER\"?",
        " first_option": "ALBERT",
        " second_option": "KURT",
        " third_option": "ANTONIO",
        " answer": "ANTONIO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ZOUMA\"?",
        " first_option": "ALBERT",
        " second_option": "MASON",
        " third_option": "KURT",
        " answer": "KURT",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CHRISTENSEN\"?",
        " first_option": "MASON",
        " second_option": "KURT",
        " third_option": "ANDREAS",
        " answer": "ANDREAS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"TOMORI\"?",
        " first_option": "AMMY",
        " second_option": "KURT",
        " third_option": "FIKAYO",
        " answer": "FIKAYO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ALONSO\"?",
        " first_option": "AMMY",
        " second_option": "MASON",
        " third_option": "MARCOS",
        " answer": "MARCOS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KANTE\"?",
        " first_option": "AMMY",
        " second_option": "OLIC",
        " third_option": "N'GOLO",
        " answer": "N'GOLO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KOVACIC\"?",
        " first_option": "MAXI",
        " second_option": "OLIC",
        " third_option": "MATEO",
        " answer": "MATEO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LOFTUS-CHEEK\"?",
        " first_option": "MARC-ANDRE",
        " second_option": "MAXI",
        " third_option": "RUBEN",
        " answer": "RUBEN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MOUNT\"?",
        " first_option": "MARC-ANDRE",
        " second_option": "BEN",
        " third_option": "MASON",
        " answer": "MASON",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ABRAHAM\"?",
        " first_option": "CALLUM",
        " second_option": "BEN",
        " third_option": "TAMMY",
        " answer": "TAMMY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GIROUD\"?",
        " first_option": "HARRY",
        " second_option": "CALLUM",
        " third_option": "OLIVIER",
        " answer": "OLIVIER",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ZAPPACOSTA\"?",
        " first_option": "HARRY",
        " second_option": "BEN",
        " third_option": "ZAPPA",
        " answer": "ZAPPA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BAKAYOKO\"?",
        " first_option": "MASON",
        " second_option": "BEN",
        " third_option": "TIEMOUE",
        " answer": "TIEMOUE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"HAZARD\"?",
        " first_option": "HAKIM",
        " second_option": "BEN",
        " third_option": "EDEN",
        " answer": "EDEN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"HAZARD\"?",
        " first_option": "HAKIM",
        " second_option": "PIERRE-EMERICK",
        " third_option": "THORGAN",
        " answer": "THORGAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"HUDSON-ODOI\"?",
        " first_option": "HAKIM",
        " second_option": "DELE",
        " third_option": "CALLUM",
        " answer": "CALLUM",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"RUDIGER\"?",
        " first_option": "HAKIM",
        " second_option": "PIERRE-EMERICK",
        " third_option": "ANTONIO",
        " answer": "ANTONIO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LLORIS\"?",
        " first_option": "PIERRE-EMERICK",
        " second_option": "JAN",
        " third_option": "HUGO",
        " answer": "HUGO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VORM\"?",
        " first_option": "SERGIO",
        " second_option": "PIERRE-EMERICK",
        " third_option": "MICHEL",
        " answer": "MICHEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SANCHEZ\"?",
        " first_option": "SERGIO",
        " second_option": "TANGUY",
        " third_option": "DAVINSON",
        " answer": "DAVINSON",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ALDERWEIRELD\"?",
        " first_option": "JOSEPH",
        " second_option": "TANGUY",
        " third_option": "TOBY",
        " answer": "TOBY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VERTONGHEN\"?",
        " first_option": "KYLIAN",
        " second_option": "JOSEPH",
        " third_option": "JAN",
        " answer": "JAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"TANGANGA\"?",
        " first_option": "KYLIAN",
        " second_option": "JOSEPH",
        " third_option": "JOPHETH",
        " answer": "JOPHETH",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"AURIER\"?",
        " first_option": "JOAO",
        " second_option": "JOSEPH",
        " third_option": "SERGE",
        " answer": "SERGE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"NDOMBELE\"?",
        " first_option": "HARRY",
        " second_option": "JOAO",
        " third_option": "TANGUY",
        " answer": "TANGUY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LO CELSO\"?",
        " first_option": "HARRY",
        " second_option": "ROBERT",
        " third_option": "GIOVANI",
        " answer": "GIOVANI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"WINKS\"?",
        " first_option": "PAULO",
        " second_option": "ROBERT",
        " third_option": "HARRY",
        " answer": "HARRY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SISSOKO\"?",
        " first_option": "ANDEL",
        " second_option": "ROBERT",
        " third_option": "MOUSSA",
        " answer": "MOUSSA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ALLI\"?",
        " first_option": "ANGEL",
        " second_option": "CALLUM",
        " third_option": "DELE",
        " answer": "DELE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MANE\"?",
        " first_option": "ANGEL",
        " second_option": "KEVIN",
        " third_option": "SADIO",
        " answer": "SADIO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MBAPPE\"?",
        " first_option": "PAUL",
        " second_option": "KEVIN",
        " third_option": "KYLIAN",
        " answer": "KYLIAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LEWANDOSKI\"?",
        " first_option": "LAUTARO",
        " second_option": "PAUL",
        " third_option": "ROBERT",
        " answer": "ROBERT",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DE JONG\"?",
        " first_option": "LAUTARO",
        " second_option": "JAN",
        " third_option": "FRENKIE",
        " answer": "FRENKIE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DE BRUYNE\"?",
        " first_option": "LAUTARO",
        " second_option": "CALLUM",
        " third_option": "KEVIN",
        " answer": "KEVIN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"AGUERO\"?",
        " first_option": "CALLUM",
        " second_option": "DUSAN",
        " third_option": "SERGIO",
        " answer": "SERGIO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DE LIGT\"?",
        " first_option": "LUIS",
        " second_option": "DUSAN",
        " third_option": "MATTHIJS",
        " answer": "MATTHIJS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SON\"?",
        " first_option": "LUIS",
        " second_option": "LUKA",
        " third_option": "HEUNG-MIN",
        " answer": "HEUNG-MIN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BENZEMA\"?",
        " first_option": "LUIS",
        " second_option": "CHRISTIAN",
        " third_option": "KARIM",
        " answer": "KARIM",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"TER STEGEN\"?",
        " first_option": "ANTONIO",
        " second_option": "CHRISTIAN",
        " third_option": "MARC-ANDRE",
        " answer": "MARC-ANDRE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"OBLAK\"?",
        " first_option": "LUSI",
        " second_option": "ANTONIO",
        " third_option": "JAN",
        " answer": "JAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GRIEZMANN\"?",
        " first_option": "LUSI",
        " second_option": "CHRISTIAN",
        " third_option": "ANTOINE",
        " answer": "ANTOINE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SUAREZ\"?",
        " first_option": "ANTIONE",
        " second_option": "CHRISTIAN",
        " third_option": "LUIS",
        " answer": "LUIS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"TADIC\"?",
        " first_option": "HAKIM",
        " second_option": "ANTIONE",
        " third_option": "DUSAN",
        " answer": "DUSAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"AUBAMEYANG\"?",
        " first_option": "HAKIM",
        " second_option": "DONNY",
        " third_option": "PIERRE-EMERICK",
        " answer": "PIERRE-EMERICK",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ZIYECH\"?",
        " first_option": "ANTIONE",
        " second_option": "DONNY",
        " third_option": "HAKIM",
        " answer": "HAKIM",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KOULIBALY\"?",
        " first_option": "SERGIO",
        " second_option": "ANTIONE",
        " third_option": "KALIDOU",
        " answer": "KALIDOU",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SANCHO\"?",
        " first_option": "SERGIO",
        " second_option": "JOSHUA",
        " third_option": "JORDAN",
        " answer": "JORDAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VAN DE BEEK\"?",
        " first_option": "SERGIO",
        " second_option": "JORDAN",
        " third_option": "DONNY",
        " answer": "DONNY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"FELIX\"?",
        " first_option": "SERGIO",
        " second_option": "JOSEPH",
        " third_option": "JOAO",
        " answer": "JOAO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"RAMOS\"?",
        " first_option": "JOAO",
        " second_option": "JOSEPH",
        " third_option": "SERGIO",
        " answer": "SERGIO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KIMMICH\"?",
        " first_option": "ANGEL",
        " second_option": "JOAO",
        " third_option": "JOSHUA",
        " answer": "JOSHUA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GNABRY\"?",
        " first_option": "ANGEL",
        " second_option": "CHRISTIAN",
        " third_option": "SERGE",
        " answer": "SERGE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DI MARIA\"?",
        " first_option": "SERGE",
        " second_option": "CHRISTIAN",
        " third_option": "ANGEL",
        " answer": "ANGEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ERIKSEN\"?",
        " first_option": "GERALD",
        " second_option": "SERGE",
        " third_option": "CHRISTIAN",
        " answer": "CHRISTIAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DYBALA\"?",
        " first_option": "GERALD",
        " second_option": "TONY",
        " third_option": "PAULO",
        " answer": "PAULO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"WIJNALDUM\"?",
        " first_option": "PAULO",
        " second_option": "TONY",
        " third_option": "GEORGINIO",
        " answer": "GEORGINIO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KROSS\"?",
        " first_option": "BRUNO",
        " second_option": "PAULO",
        " third_option": "TONI",
        " answer": "TONI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MODRIC\"?",
        " first_option": "BRUNO",
        " second_option": "JAMIE",
        " third_option": "LUKA",
        " answer": "LUKA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MARTINEZ\"?",
        " first_option": "LUKA",
        " second_option": "JAMIE",
        " third_option": "LAUTARO",
        " answer": "LAUTARO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VARDY\"?",
        " first_option": "MIRALEM",
        " second_option": "LUKA",
        " third_option": "JAMIE",
        " answer": "JAMIE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MAHREZ\"?",
        " first_option": "MIRALEM",
        " second_option": "ROMEO",
        " third_option": "RIYAD",
        " answer": "RIYAD",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"PJANIC\"?",
        " first_option": "RIYAD",
        " second_option": "ROMEO",
        " third_option": "MIRALEM",
        " answer": "MIRALEM",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LUKAKU\"?",
        " first_option": "ERLING",
        " second_option": "RIYAD",
        " third_option": "ROMELU",
        " answer": "ROMELU",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BARBOSA\"?",
        " first_option": "ERLING",
        " second_option": "AYMERIC",
        " third_option": "GABRIEL",
        " answer": "GABRIEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"HAALAND\"?",
        " first_option": "GABRIEL",
        " second_option": "AYMERIC",
        " third_option": "ERLING",
        " answer": "ERLING",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LAPORTE\"?",
        " first_option": "EDINSON",
        " second_option": "GABRIEL",
        " third_option": "AYMERIC",
        " answer": "AYMERIC",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"POGBA\"?",
        " first_option": "EDINSON",
        " second_option": "DANI",
        " third_option": "PAULO",
        " answer": "PAULO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CAVANI\"?",
        " first_option": "PAUL",
        " second_option": "DANI",
        " third_option": "EDINSON",
        " answer": "EDINSON",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ALVES\"?",
        " first_option": "MAURO",
        " second_option": "PAUL",
        " third_option": "DANI",
        " answer": "DANI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"WERNER\"?",
        " first_option": "MAURO",
        " second_option": "CIRO",
        " third_option": "TIMO",
        " answer": "TIMO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ICARDI\"?",
        " first_option": "TIMO",
        " second_option": "CIRO",
        " third_option": "MAURO",
        " answer": "MAURO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"IMMOBILE\"?",
        " first_option": "JORDAN",
        " second_option": "TIMO",
        " third_option": "CIRO",
        " answer": "CIRO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ZAPATA\"?",
        " first_option": "GEORGE",
        " second_option": "LUCAS",
        " third_option": "DUVAN",
        " answer": "DUVAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ALBA\"?",
        " first_option": "DUVAN",
        " second_option": "LUCAS",
        " third_option": "JORDI",
        " answer": "JORDI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MOURA\"?",
        " first_option": "GEORGE",
        " second_option": "DUVAN",
        " third_option": "LUCAS",
        " answer": "LUCAS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SILVA\"?",
        " first_option": "GEROG",
        " second_option": "MARCUS",
        " third_option": "THIAGO",
        " answer": "THIAGO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"FERNANDES\"?",
        " first_option": "TAMMY",
        " second_option": "MARCUS",
        " third_option": "BRUNO",
        " answer": "BRUNO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CHIELLINI\"?",
        " first_option": "BRUNO",
        " second_option": "MARCUS",
        " third_option": "GIORGIO",
        " answer": "GIORGIO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"RASHFORD\"?",
        " first_option": "BRUNO",
        " second_option": "DRIES",
        " third_option": "MARCUS",
        " answer": "MARCUS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VARANE\"?",
        " first_option": "DRIES",
        " second_option": "MEMPHIS",
        " third_option": "RAPHAEL",
        " answer": "RAPHAEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DEPAY\"?",
        " first_option": "RAPHAEL",
        " second_option": "DRIES",
        " third_option": "MEMPHIS",
        " answer": "MEMPHIS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MERTENS\"?",
        " first_option": "RAPHAEL",
        " second_option": "MEMPHIS",
        " third_option": "DRIES",
        " answer": "DRIES",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BUSQUETS\"?",
        " first_option": "DRIES",
        " second_option": "MEMPHIS",
        " third_option": "SERGIO",
        " answer": "SERGIO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VERATTI\"?",
        " first_option": "SERGE",
        " second_option": "DRIES",
        " third_option": "MARCO",
        " answer": "MARCO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"PIQUE\"?",
        " first_option": "SERGE",
        " second_option": "MARCO",
        " third_option": "GERARD",
        " answer": "GERARD",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"PUKKI\"?",
        " first_option": "GERARD",
        " second_option": "MARCO",
        " third_option": "TEEMU",
        " answer": "TEEMU",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GODIN\"?",
        " first_option": "TEEMU",
        " second_option": "GERARD",
        " third_option": "DIEGO",
        " answer": "DIEGO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"HAVERTZ\"?",
        " first_option": "TEEMU",
        " second_option": "DIEGO",
        " third_option": "KAI",
        " answer": "KAI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ABRAHAM\"?",
        " first_option": "KAI",
        " second_option": "DIEGO",
        " third_option": "TAMMY",
        " answer": "TAMMY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"HAKIMI\"?",
        " first_option": "KAI",
        " second_option": "ACHRAF",
        " third_option": "TEEMU",
        " answer": "ACHRAF",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SANE\"?",
        " first_option": "ACHRAF",
        " second_option": "LEROY",
        " third_option": "TEEMU",
        " answer": "LEROY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DE GEA\"?",
        " first_option": "ACHRAF",
        " second_option": "DAVID",
        " third_option": "LEROY",
        " answer": "DAVID",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"QUAGLIARELLA\"?",
        " first_option": "LEROY",
        " second_option": "FABIO",
        " third_option": "DAVID",
        " answer": "FABIO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GUEYE\"?",
        " first_option": "FABIO",
        " second_option": "IDRISSA",
        " third_option": "DAVID",
        " answer": "IDRISSA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"IBRAHIMOVIC\"?",
        " first_option": "FABIO",
        " second_option": "ZLATAN",
        " third_option": "SANTI",
        " answer": "ZLATAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CAZORLA\"?",
        " first_option": "FABIO",
        " second_option": "SANTI",
        " third_option": "ALEXANDRE",
        " answer": "SANTI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"HANDANOVIC\"?",
        " first_option": "SANTI",
        " second_option": "SAMIR",
        " third_option": "ALEXANDRE",
        " answer": "SAMIR",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LACAZETTE\"?",
        " first_option": "SAMIR",
        " second_option": "ALEXANDRE",
        " third_option": "SANTI",
        " answer": "ALEXANDRE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"AREOLA\"?",
        " first_option": "SANTI",
        " second_option": "ALPHONSE",
        " third_option": "DANIEL",
        " answer": "ALPHONSE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"FERNADEZ\"?",
        " first_option": "ALPHONSE",
        " second_option": "NACHO",
        " third_option": "DANIEL",
        " answer": "NACHO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CARVAJAL\"?",
        " first_option": "ALPHONSE",
        " second_option": "DANIEL",
        " third_option": "NACHO",
        " answer": "DANIEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KROOS\"?",
        " first_option": "ALPHONSE",
        " second_option": "TONI",
        " third_option": "DANIEL",
        " answer": "TONI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VALVERDE\"?",
        " first_option": "ALPHONSE",
        " second_option": "FEDERICO",
        " third_option": "TONI",
        " answer": "FEDERICO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MODRIC\"?",
        " first_option": "TONI",
        " second_option": "LUKA",
        " third_option": "MARK",
        " answer": "LUKA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"JUNIOR\"?",
        " first_option": "TONI",
        " second_option": "VINICIUS",
        " third_option": "MARK",
        " answer": "VINICIUS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ASENSIO\"?",
        " first_option": "VINICIUS",
        " second_option": "MARKO",
        " third_option": "TONI",
        " answer": "MARKO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VASQUEZ\"?",
        " first_option": "VINICIUS",
        " second_option": "LUCAS",
        " third_option": "MARCO",
        " answer": "LUCAS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"JOVIC\"?",
        " first_option": "VINICIUS",
        " second_option": "LUKA",
        " third_option": "IKER",
        " answer": "LUKA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BALE\"?",
        " first_option": "IKER",
        " second_option": "GARETH",
        " third_option": "LUKA",
        " answer": "GARETH",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CASILLAS\"?",
        " first_option": "GARETH",
        " second_option": "IKER",
        " third_option": "GONZALEZ",
        " answer": "IKER",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LOPEZ\"?",
        " first_option": "MICHEL",
        " second_option": "DIEGO",
        " third_option": "LUKA",
        " answer": "DIEGO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"RAUL\"?",
        " first_option": "ROBERTO",
        " second_option": "GONZALEZ",
        " third_option": "MICHEL",
        " answer": "GONZALEZ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CARLOS\"?",
        " first_option": "MICHEL",
        " second_option": "ROBERTO",
        " third_option": "ESTEBAN",
        " answer": "ROBERTO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SALGADO\"?",
        " first_option": "ROBERT",
        " second_option": "MICHEL",
        " third_option": "ESTEBAN",
        " answer": "MICHEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CAMBIASSO\"?",
        " first_option": "ROBERT",
        " second_option": "ESTEBAN",
        " third_option": "LUIS",
        " answer": "ESTEBAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"FIGO\"?",
        " first_option": "ROBERT",
        " second_option": "LUIS",
        " third_option": "FERNANDO",
        " answer": "LUIS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LLORENTE\"?",
        " first_option": "ROBERT",
        " second_option": "FERNANDO",
        " third_option": "KEYLOR",
        " answer": "FERNANDO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"NAVAS\"?",
        " first_option": "ROBERT",
        " second_option": "KEYLOR",
        " third_option": "DIEGO",
        " answer": "KEYLOR",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LLORENTE\"?",
        " first_option": "ROBERT",
        " second_option": "DIEGO",
        " third_option": "ALVARO",
        " answer": "DIEGO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ARBELOA\"?",
        " first_option": "ROBERT",
        " second_option": "ALVARO",
        " third_option": "DIEGO",
        " answer": "ALVARO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KHEDIRA\"?",
        " first_option": "JAMES",
        " second_option": "SAMI",
        " third_option": "DIEGO",
        " answer": "SAMI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"RODRIGUEZ\"?",
        " first_option": "SAMIR",
        " second_option": "JAMES",
        " third_option": "DIEGO",
        " answer": "JAMES",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ODEGAARD\"?",
        " first_option": "SAMIR",
        " second_option": "MARTIN",
        " third_option": "JAMES",
        " answer": "MARTIN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ERIKSEN\"?",
        " first_option": "SAMIR",
        " second_option": "CHRISTIAN",
        " third_option": "JAMES",
        " answer": "CHRISTIAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LENGLET\"?",
        " first_option": "SAMIR",
        " second_option": "CLEMENT",
        " third_option": "CHRISTIAN",
        " answer": "CLEMENT",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"UMTITI\"?",
        " first_option": "CLARENCE",
        " second_option": "SAMUEL",
        " third_option": "CHRISTIAN",
        " answer": "SAMUEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ROBERTO\"?",
        " first_option": "SAMUEL",
        " second_option": "SERGIO",
        " third_option": "CLARENCE",
        " answer": "SERGIO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BUSQUETS\"?",
        " first_option": "SAMUEL",
        " second_option": "SERGIO",
        " third_option": "SERGIO",
        " answer": "SERGIO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"RAKITIC\"?",
        " first_option": "ARTURO",
        " second_option": "IVAN",
        " third_option": "SERGIO",
        " answer": "IVAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VIDAL\"?",
        " first_option": "IVAN",
        " second_option": "ARTURO",
        " third_option": "SERGIO",
        " answer": "ARTURO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"FATI\"?",
        " first_option": "IVAN",
        " second_option": "ANSU",
        " third_option": "ARTURO",
        " answer": "ANSU",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"TURAN\"?",
        " first_option": "ARTURO",
        " second_option": "ARDA",
        " third_option": "ANDU",
        " answer": "ARDA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DEMBELE\"?",
        " first_option": "ARDA",
        " second_option": "OUSMANE",
        " third_option": "ANDU",
        " answer": "OUSMANE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VALDES\"?",
        " first_option": "ARDA",
        " second_option": "VICTOR",
        " third_option": "BASTIAN",
        " answer": "VICTOR",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"PUYOL\"?",
        " first_option": "BASTIAN",
        " second_option": "CARLOS",
        " third_option": "VICTOR",
        " answer": "CARLOS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SCHWEINSTEIGER\"?",
        " first_option": "GIANLUIGI",
        " second_option": "BASTIAN",
        " third_option": "VICTOR",
        " answer": "BASTIAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VAN BRONCKHORST\"?",
        " first_option": "GIANLUIGI",
        " second_option": "GIOVANNI",
        " third_option": "JULIANO",
        " answer": "GIOVANNI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ZAMBROTTA\"?",
        " first_option": "GIANLUCA",
        " second_option": "JULIANO",
        " third_option": "MARK",
        " answer": "GIANLUCA",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BELLETI\"?",
        " first_option": "JULIANO",
        " second_option": "THIAGO",
        " third_option": "MARK",
        " answer": "JULIANO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VAN BOMMEL\"?",
        " first_option": "MARK",
        " second_option": "THIAGO",
        " third_option": "ANDRES",
        " answer": "MARK",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MOTTA\"?",
        " first_option": "THIAGO",
        " second_option": "ANDRES",
        " third_option": "MARMO",
        " answer": "THIAGO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"INIESTA\"?",
        " first_option": "ANDRES",
        " second_option": "THIAGO",
        " third_option": "MARMO",
        " answer": "ANDRES",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GUILY\"?",
        " first_option": "LUDOVIC",
        " second_option": "THIAGO",
        " third_option": "ANDRES",
        " answer": "LUDOVIC",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SAVIOLA\"?",
        " first_option": "JAVIER",
        " second_option": "THIAGO",
        " third_option": "SAMUL",
        " answer": "JAVIER",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ETO'O\"?",
        " first_option": "SAMUEL",
        " second_option": "THIAGO",
        " third_option": "JAVIER",
        " answer": "SAMUEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GUDJOHNSEN\"?",
        " first_option": "EIDUR",
        " second_option": "THIAGO",
        " third_option": "SAMUEL",
        " answer": "EIDUR",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KEITA\"?",
        " first_option": "SEYDOU",
        " second_option": "THIAGO",
        " third_option": "EIDUR",
        " answer": "SEYDOU",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VILLA\"?",
        " first_option": "DAVID",
        " second_option": "EIDUR",
        " third_option": "SEYDOU",
        " answer": "DAVID",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MARADONA\"?",
        " first_option": "DIEGO",
        " second_option": "DAVID",
        " third_option": "SEYDOU",
        " answer": "DIEGO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ROSSI\"?",
        " first_option": "PAOLO",
        " second_option": "DAVID",
        " third_option": "LEV",
        " answer": "PAOLO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"WEAH\"?",
        " first_option": "GEORGE",
        " second_option": "LEV",
        " third_option": "PAOLO",
        " answer": "GEORGE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"YASHIN\"?",
        " first_option": "GEORGE",
        " second_option": "LEV",
        " third_option": "PAOLO",
        " answer": "LEV",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"KEEGAN\"?",
        " first_option": "GEORGE",
        " second_option": "KEVIN",
        " third_option": "KENNY",
        " answer": "KEVIN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DALGISH\"?",
        " first_option": "GEORGE",
        " second_option": "KENNY",
        " third_option": "HERNANDEZ",
        " answer": "KENNY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BUFFON\"?",
        " first_option": "RUUD",
        " second_option": "GIANLUIGI",
        " third_option": "HERNANDEZ",
        " answer": "GIANLUIGI",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"XAVI\"?",
        " first_option": "LOTHAR",
        " second_option": "HERNANDEZ",
        " third_option": "RUUD",
        " answer": "HERNANDEZ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MOORE\"?",
        " first_option": "LOTHAR",
        " second_option": "BOBBY",
        " third_option": "HERNANDEZ",
        " answer": "BOBBY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CHARLTON\"?",
        " first_option": "LOTHAR",
        " second_option": "BOBBY",
        " third_option": "RUUD",
        " answer": "BOBBY",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MATTHAUS\"?",
        " first_option": "RUUD",
        " second_option": "LOTHAR",
        " third_option": "BOBBY",
        " answer": "LOTHAR",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"GULLIT\"?",
        " first_option": "FRANK",
        " second_option": "RUUD",
        " third_option": "BOBBY",
        " answer": "RUUD",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"VAN BASTEN\"?",
        " first_option": "FRANK",
        " second_option": "MARCO",
        " third_option": "GERARD",
        " answer": "MARCO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BEST\"?",
        " first_option": "FRANK",
        " second_option": "GEORGE",
        " third_option": "IAN",
        " answer": "GEORGE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BARESI\"?",
        " first_option": "GEORGE",
        " second_option": "FRANCO",
        " third_option": "IAN",
        " answer": "FRANCO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"WRIGHT\"?",
        " first_option": "FERENC",
        " second_option": "IAN",
        " third_option": "GEORGE",
        " answer": "IAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SEEDORF\"?",
        " first_option": "FERENC",
        " second_option": "CLARENCE",
        " third_option": "EDGAR",
        " answer": "CLARENCE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DAVIDS\"?",
        " first_option": "FERENC",
        " second_option": "EDGAR",
        " third_option": "ALFREDO",
        " answer": "EDGAR",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"PUSKAS\"?",
        " first_option": "ALFREDO",
        " second_option": "FERENC",
        " third_option": "GERD",
        " answer": "FERENC",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MALDINI\"?",
        " first_option": "PATRICK",
        " second_option": "PAOLO",
        " third_option": "GERD",
        " answer": "PAOLO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MULLER\"?",
        " first_option": "PATRICK",
        " second_option": "GERD",
        " third_option": "ALFRED",
        " answer": "GERD",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"SNEIDJER\"?",
        " first_option": "ALFRED",
        " second_option": "MIKAEL",
        " third_option": "MANE",
        " answer": "MANE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"DI STEFANO\"?",
        " first_option": "ALFREDO",
        " second_option": "PHILIPP",
        " third_option": "MICHEL",
        " answer": "ALFREDO",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"PLATINI\"?",
        " first_option": "MICHEL",
        " second_option": "PHILIPP",
        " third_option": "FRANZ",
        " answer": "MICHEL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ZIDANE\"?",
        " first_option": "ZINEDINE",
        " second_option": "PHILIPP",
        " third_option": "JOHAN",
        " answer": "ZINEDINE",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CRYUFF\"?",
        " first_option": "JOHAN",
        " second_option": "PHILIPP",
        " third_option": "JEROME",
        " answer": "JOHAN",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BECKENBAUER\"?",
        " first_option": "FRANZ",
        " second_option": "PHILIPP",
        " third_option": "DAVID",
        " answer": "FRANZ",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"LAHM\"?",
        " first_option": "PHILIPP",
        " second_option": "MATS",
        " third_option": "DAVID",
        " answer": "PHILIPP",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"BOATENG\"?",
        " first_option": "JEROME",
        " second_option": "THAMES",
        " third_option": "DAVID",
        " answer": "JEROME",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"ALABA\"?",
        " first_option": "DAVID",
        " second_option": "THAMES",
        " third_option": "MATS",
        " answer": "DAVID",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"MULLER\"?",
        " first_option": "THOMAS",
        " second_option": "MATS",
        " third_option": "MICHEAL",
        " answer": "THOMAS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"HUMMELS\"?",
        " first_option": "MATS",
        " second_option": "THOMAS",
        " third_option": "MICHEAL",
        " answer": "MATS",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of this popular player  \"CARRICK\"?",
        " first_option": "MICHEAL",
        " second_option": "MATS",
        " third_option": "THOMAS",
        " answer": "MICHEAL",
        " difficulty": "EASY",
        "null": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    }
]